<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<!DOCTYPE pkgmetadata SYSTEM "http://www.gentoo.org/dtd/metadata.dtd">
<pkgmetadata>
  <maintainer type="project">
    <email>b@edevau.net</email>
    <name>Andreas Billmeier</name>
  </maintainer>
  <upstream>
    <remote-id type="pypi">home-assistant</remote-id>
    <remote-id type="github">home-assistant/core</remote-id>
    <doc>https://www.home-assistant.io/docs/</doc>
    <maintainer>
      <email>hello@home-assistant.io</email>
      <name>The Home Assistant Authors</name>
    </maintainer>
  </upstream>
  <use>
    <flag name="abode">The Abode integration allows you to integrate your Abode Home Security systems into Home Assistant and use its alarm system and sensors to trigger automations.</flag>
    <flag name="acaia">The Acaia integration allows you to control Acaia scales through Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="accuweather">The AccuWeather integration uses the AccuWeather web service as a source for weather data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="acer_projector">The acer_projector switch platform allows you to control the state of RS232 connected projectors from Acer.</flag>
    <flag name="acmeda">The Rollease Acmeda Automate integration allows you to control and monitor covers via your Rollease Acmeda Automate hub. The integrations communicates directly with hubs on the local network, rather than connecting via the cloud or via RS-485. Devices are represented as a cover for monitoring and control as well as a sensor for monitoring battery condition.</flag>
    <flag name="adax">The Adax integration integrates Adax heaters into Home Assistant and can be configured to use a local or cloud interface.</flag>
    <flag name="adguard">AdGuard Home is a network-wide DNS server that supports ad, tracker,and adult content blocking. The AdGuard integration allows you to control andmonitor your AdGuard Home instance in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ads">The ADS (automation device specification) describes a device-independent and fieldbus independent interface for communication between Beckhoff automation devices running TwinCAT and other devices implementing this interface.</flag>
    <flag name="advantage_air">The Advantage Air integration allows you to control Advantage Air Air Conditioning controllers into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="aemet">The AEMET weather platform uses AEMET OpenData as a source for current meteorological data for your location. AEMET stands for “Agencia Estatal de Meteorología”, which is the Spanish Meteorological Agency.</flag>
    <flag name="aftership">The aftership platform allows one to track deliveries by AfterShip, a service that supports 490+ couriers worldwide. To use the tracking API functionality, the Pro plan is required.</flag>
    <flag name="agent_dvr">Agent DVR is a free* software DVR solution for Windows 10, Mac and Linux. Agent DVR runs as a service or console application and can access and control a huge range of third party cameras with advanced motion detection, including DeepStack integration for object recognition. The iSpyConnect website provides secured (SSL) remote access without port forwarding needed.</flag>
    <flag name="airgradient">The AirGradient integration will fetch data from your AirGradient devices.AirGradient creates indoor and outdoor air quality monitors that enable you know if the air quality is healthy or not. They measure metrics such as PM2.5, CO2, TVOCs, and NOx. Both the software and hardware are open-source, allowing you to customize or extend the device functionality.</flag>
    <flag name="airly">The Airly integration uses the Airly web service as a source for air quality data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="airnow">The AirNow integration uses the AirNow web serviceas a source for air quality data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="airq">The air-Q integration allows integrating the sensors, provided by your air-Q device, into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="airthings_ble">Integrates Airthings BLE sensors into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="airthings">Integrates Airthings sensors into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="airtouch4">The AirTouch 4 integration allows you to control Ducted Air Conditioning Systems that are using the AirTouch 4 controller. Currently, this integration only supports AirTouch 4 controllers with the Individual Temperature Control (ITC) modules.</flag>
    <flag name="airtouch5">The AirTouch 5 integration allows you to control ducted air conditioning systems that are using the AirTouch 5 controller.</flag>
    <flag name="airvisual">The airvisual sensor platform queries the AirVisual cloud API for air quality data. Data can be collected via latitude/longitude or city/state/country.</flag>
    <flag name="airvisual_pro">The AirVisual Pro integration allows users to retrieve data from an AirVisual Node/Pro unit. Communication with the device occurs over the local network.</flag>
    <flag name="airzone_cloud">This integration interacts with the Cloud API of Airzone devices.</flag>
    <flag name="airzone">This integration interacts with the Local API of Airzone HVAC zoning systems.</flag>
    <flag name="alarmdecoder">The AlarmDecoder integration will allow Home Assistant users who own either a DSC or Honeywell alarm panel to leverage their alarm system and its sensors to provide Home Assistant with rich information about their homes. Connectivity between Home Assistant and the alarm panel is accomplished through a device produced by Nu Tech Software Solutions, known as the AlarmDecoder. The AlarmDecoder devices provide a serial, TCP/IP socket or USB interface to the alarm panel, where it emulates an alarm keypad.</flag>
    <flag name="alpha_vantage">The alpha_vantage sensor platform uses Alpha Vantage to monitor the stock market. This platform also provides detail about exchange rates.</flag>
    <flag name="amazon_polly">The amazon_polly text-to-speech platform that works with Amazon Polly to create the spoken output.Polly is a paid service via Amazon Web Services. There is a free tier for the first 12 months and then a charge per million characters afterwards.</flag>
    <flag name="amberelectric">Amber is an Australian electricity retailer that provides access to wholesale electricity prices. Customers monitor the wholesale price and shift their energy usage to cheaper, greener times. This saves them money and supports the shift to a more renewably-powered Australia.</flag>
    <flag name="ambient_network">The Ambient Weather Network integration retrieves local weather station informationvia the Ambient Weather Network.</flag>
    <flag name="ambient_station">The Ambient Weather Station integration retrieves local weather informationvia personal weather stations from Ambient Weather.</flag>
    <flag name="amcrest">The amcrest camera platform allows you to integrate your Amcrest or Dahua IP camera or doorbell in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ampio">The ampio air quality platform will query the open data API of ampio.pl to monitor air quality sensor station.</flag>
    <flag name="analytics_insights">The Analytics Insights integration allows you to get integration usage statistics into Home Assistant.The data comes from Home Assistant Analytics.For more information about the component that collects analytics, checkout Analytics.</flag>
    <flag name="android_ip_webcam">The Android IP Webcam integration connects with Android IP Webcam to turn any Android phone or tablet into a network camera with multiple viewing options.</flag>
    <flag name="androidtv">The Android Debug Bridge integration allows you to control an Android device or Amazon Fire TV device.</flag>
    <flag name="androidtv_remote">The Android TV Remote integration allows you to control an Android TV and launching apps. For this to work, the Android TV device needs to have Android TV Remote Service which is pre-installed on most devices (Fire TV devices are a notable exception).</flag>
    <flag name="anel_pwrctrl">The anel_pwrctrl switch platform allows you to control ANEL PwrCtrl devices on firmware 6.x and older. ANEL PwrCtrl devices on firmware 7.x are not supported.</flag>
    <flag name="anova">The Anova sensor platform allows you to control Anova sous vides with Wi-Fi capability.</flag>
    <flag name="anthemav">Both Anthem’s current and last generation of A/V receivers and processors support IP-based network control. This Home Assistant integration adds proper “local push” support for any of these receivers on your network.</flag>
    <flag name="anthropic">The Anthropic integrations adds a conversation agent powered by Anthropic, such as Claude 3.5 Sonnet, in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="aosmith">The A. O. Smith integration allows you to control a compatible A. O. Smith iCOMM-enabled water heater from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="apache_kafka">The Apache Kafka integration sends all state changes to aApache Kafka topic.</flag>
    <flag name="apcupsd">apcupsd status information can be integrated into Home Assistant when the Network Information Server (NIS) is configured on the APC device.</flag>
    <flag name="apple_tv">The Apple TV integration allows you to control an Apple TV (any generation).</flag>
    <flag name="apprise">The Apprise service is an all-in-one solution to open up Home Assistant to just about every Notification platform (such as Amazon SNS, Discord, Telegram, Slack, MSTeams, Twilio, etc.)</flag>
    <flag name="aprilaire">The AprilAire integration allows you to control an AprilAire thermostat.</flag>
    <flag name="aprs">The aprs (Automatic Packet Reporting System) device tracker integration connects to the APRS-IS network for tracking amateur radio devices.</flag>
    <flag name="apsystems">The APsystems integration allows you to read the data from your APsystems EZ1 microinverter. It also allows you to set the output limit to anything above 30 watts.</flag>
    <flag name="aquacell">AquaCell is a water-softening device made by Culligan. The AquaCell integration allows you to monitor your AquaCell device in Home Assistant.You will need your Aquacell account information as used in the AquaCell app.</flag>
    <flag name="aqualogic">The AquaLogic integration provides connectivity to a Hayward/Goldline AquaLogic/ProLogic pool controller. Note that an RS-485 to Ethernet adapter connected to the pool controller is required.</flag>
    <flag name="aquostv">The aquostv platform allows you to control a Sharp Aquos TV.</flag>
    <flag name="aranet">Integrates Aranet devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="arcam_fmj">The arcam_fmj integration allows you to control Arcam Receivers and Processors from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="arris_tg2492lg">This platform allows you to detect presence by looking at connected devices to an Arris TG2492LG router.</flag>
    <flag name="aruba">This platform allows you to detect presence by looking at connected devices to an Aruba Instant device.</flag>
    <flag name="arve">The Arve integration provides the ability to monitor real-life air quality data, as measured by your Arve device.</flag>
    <flag name="aseko_pool_live">The Aseko Pool Live integration allows you to monitor your Aseko ASIN Aqua dosing systems and Aseko ASIN Pool controllers.</flag>
    <flag name="assist_pipeline">The Assist pipeline integration provides the foundation for the Assist voice assistant in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="asuswrt">The ASUSWRT integration can connect Home Assistant to a ASUS router that runs on ASUSWRT firmware.</flag>
    <flag name="atag">The Atag integration allows Home Assistant to connect to Atag One thermostats, reporting and setting its status.The integration implements the following platforms:</flag>
    <flag name="aten_pe">The aten_pe integration lets you control ATEN Rack PDUs from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="atome">The atome sensor platform is retrieving the consumption of your home from the Direct Energy Atome electric meter.This special little device is connected to a Linky Electric Meter, and sends live data to a cloud platform.</flag>
    <flag name="august">The august integration allows you to integrate your August and some Yale Access devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="aurora_abb_powerone">This implements a direct RS485 connection to a solar inverter in thePVI-3.0/3.6/4.2-TL-OUTD ABB series, and may work on others.The inverter was formerly made by PowerOne who got taken over by ABB.</flag>
    <flag name="aurora">The aurora platform uses the NOAA Aurora Forecast action to let you know if an aurora might be visible at your home location in the next 30 minutes, based off of current solar flare activity.</flag>
    <flag name="aussie_broadband">The Aussie Broadband integration displays various service metrics using the Aussie Broadband API.</flag>
    <flag name="autarco">The Autarco integration allows you to gather data from the cloud API of Autarco and use it in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="avea">Elgato Avea is a Bluetooth light bulb that is no longer supported by the manufacturer. The avea integration allows you to control all your Avea bulbs with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="avion">Support for the Avi-on Bluetooth dimmer switch Avi-on.</flag>
    <flag name="awair">The Awair integration will fetch data from your Awair devices.</flag>
    <flag name="aws">The aws integration provides a single place to interact with Amazon Web Services. Currently it provides a notification platform that can send a message to AWS SQS, AWS SNS, or invoke AWS Lambda functions.</flag>
    <flag name="axis">Axis Communications devices are surveillance cameras, speakers, access control and other security-related network connected hardware. Event API works with firmware 5.50 and newer.</flag>
    <flag name="azure_data_explorer">Azure Data Explorer is a high-performance time-series database, query engine, and dashboarding tool. The Home Assistant Azure Data Explorer integration allows you to hook into the Home Assistant event bus and forward events to Azure Data Explorer for analytics and dashboarding. From here, data can be viewed in building dashboards, PowerBi, and Grafana, among others.</flag>
    <flag name="azure_devops">The Azure DevOps integration allows you to control and monitor yourAzure DevOps instance in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="azure_event_hub">The Azure Event Hub integration allows you to hook into the Home Assistant event bus and send events to Azure Event Hub or to an Azure IoT Hub.</flag>
    <flag name="azure_service_bus">The Azure Service Bus integration allows you to send messages to Azure Service Bus from within Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="azure_storage">This integration allows you to use Azure storage accounts for use with Home Assistant Backups.</flag>
    <flag name="backup">The Backup integration is used by all installation types to create and restore backups.</flag>
    <flag name="baf">Integrates Big Ass Fans devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="baidu">The baidu text-to-speech platform uses Baidu TTS engine to read a text with natural sounding voices.</flag>
    <flag name="balboa">The Balboa Spa Client integration adds support for Balboa Spa WiFi Modules to be used within Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bang_olufsen">The Bang &amp; Olufsen integration enables control of some of the features of certain Bang &amp; Olufsen devices through Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bbox">The bbox integration uses the Bbox Modem Router from the French Internet provider Bouygues Telecom. Sensors are mainly bandwidth measures.</flag>
    <flag name="beewi_smartclim">The beewi_smartclim sensor platform allows one to monitor room or external temperature and humidity. The BeeWi SmartClim BLE is a Bluetooth Low Energy sensor device that monitors temperature from a room or a garden from your smartphone by using an APP. Use this integration to track these metrics from any location thanks to Home Assistant, as well as to create some automation scripts based on your room’s temperature.</flag>
    <flag name="bitcoin">The bitcoin sensor platform displays various details about the Bitcoin network.</flag>
    <flag name="bizkaibus">The bizkaibus sensor will give you the time until the next bus in the selected stop.</flag>
    <flag name="blackbird">The blackbird platform allows you to control Monoprice Blackbird Matrix Switch (8x8) using a serial or IP connection, this integration does not support the 4x4 matrix switch.</flag>
    <flag name="blebox">BleBox produces small, low-power, surprisingly affordable, feature-rich WiFi devices for serverless home automation.</flag>
    <flag name="blink">The Blink integration lets you view camera images and motion events from Blink camera and security systems.</flag>
    <flag name="blockchain">The Blockchain sensor platform displays Bitcoin wallet balances from blockchain.com.</flag>
    <flag name="blue_current">Blue Current is an Dutch company that makes electric car chargers.</flag>
    <flag name="bluemaestro">Integrates BlueMaestro devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bluesound">The bluesound platform allows you to control your Bluesound HiFi wireless speakers and audio integrations from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bluetooth">The Bluetooth integration will detect nearby Bluetooth devices. Discovered devices will show up in the discovered section on the integrations page in the configuration panel.</flag>
    <flag name="bluetooth_tracker">This tracker discovers new devices on boot and tracks Bluetooth devices periodically based on interval_seconds value. It is not required to pair the devices with each other! Devices discovered are stored with ‘bt_’ as the prefix for device MAC addresses in known_devices.yaml.</flag>
    <flag name="bmw_connected_drive">The BMW Connected Drive integration lets you retrieve data of your BMW or MINI vehicle from the MyBMW portal (previously BMW Connected Drive).</flag>
    <flag name="bond">The Bond integration allows you to control appliances through your Bond Bridge. Duplicates your RF remote control.</flag>
    <flag name="bosch_shc">The Bosch SHC integration allows you to connect your Bosch Smart Home Controller to Home Assistant in order to control and monitor your Bosch Smart Home devices.</flag>
    <flag name="braviatv">The Bravia TV integration allows you to control a Sony Bravia TV.</flag>
    <flag name="bring">The Bring! integration allows you to sync your Bring! shopping lists with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="broadlink">The Broadlink integration allows you to control and monitor Broadlink universal remotes, smart plugs, power strips, switches and sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="brother">The Brother Printer integration allows you to read current data from your local Brother printer.</flag>
    <flag name="brottsplatskartan">The brottsplatskartan sensor allows one to track reported incidents occurring in a given area. Incidents include anything reported to Brottsplatskartan. The sensor only counts incidents from the current day.</flag>
    <flag name="brunt">The Brunt Blind Energy integration allows one to control Blind Engines by Brunt. To use it, you need a Brunt App Account. All Brunt Blind devices registered to your account are automatically added to your Home Assistant with the names given them through the Brunt app.</flag>
    <flag name="bryant_evolution">The Bryant Evolution integration lets you control Bryant Evolution HVAC systems.</flag>
    <flag name="bsblan">The BSB-Lan integration integrates BSBLan devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bt_home_hub_5">This platform offers presence detection by looking at connected devices to a BT Home Hub 5 based router.</flag>
    <flag name="bthome">Integrates BTHome BLE devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="bt_smarthub">This platform offers presence detection by looking at connected devices to a BT Smart Hub based router.This router is sometimes referred to as the BT Home Hub 6.</flag>
    <flag name="buienradar">The Buienradar integration uses buienradar.nl as a source for current meteorological data for your location. The weather forecast is delivered by Buienradar, who provides a web service that provides detailed weather information for users in The Netherlands.</flag>
    <flag name="caldav">The CalDAV integration allows you to connect your WebDAV calendar to Home Assistantas one of these entity types:</flag>
    <flag name="cambridge_audio">The Cambridge Audio integration allows you to control all receivers and streamers that support the StreamMagic app.</flag>
    <flag name="camera">The camera integration allows you to use IP cameras with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="canary">The Canary integration allows you to integrate your Canary devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="cast">Configuration To add the Google Cast integration to your Home Assistant instance, use this My button:</flag>
    <flag name="ccm15">The CCM15 integration allows you to integrate Midea CCM15 devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="chacon_dio">Chacon Dio devices are connected home devices that can be controlled via RF 433 MHz or Wi-Fi.This integrations gives you access to the Wi-Fi connection so that Home Assistant can list your Chacon Dio devices and interact with them in real time, the same way the vendor’s smartphone application does.</flag>
    <flag name="channels">The Channels platform allows you to control Channels from Home Assistant. Play, pause, seek, or skip commercials on an instance of Channels that is running on your network.</flag>
    <flag name="cisco_ios">This is a presence detection scanner for Cisco IOS devices.</flag>
    <flag name="cisco_mobility_express">This is a presence detection scanner for Cisco Mobility Express wireless controllers.</flag>
    <flag name="cisco_webex_teams">The cisco_webex_teams notification platform allows you to deliver rich notifications from Home Assistant to Cisco Webex (formerly known as Cisco Spark or Cisco Webex Teams).</flag>
    <flag name="clementine">The clementine platform allows you to control a Clementine Music Player.</flag>
    <flag name="cloudflare">With the Cloudflare integration, you can keep your Cloudflare DNS records up to date.</flag>
    <flag name="cloud">The Home Assistant Cloud allows you to quickly integrate your local Home Assistant with various cloud services like Amazon Alexa and Google Assistant. It also enables a secure remote connection, speech-to-text, text-to-speech, an offsite backup location, Webhooks support, and better WebRTC. Learn more.</flag>
    <flag name="cmus">The cmus platform allows you to control a cmus music player on a remote or local machine from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="co2signal">The Electricity Maps sensor platform (formerly known as CO2Signal) queries the Electricity Maps API for the CO2 intensity of a specific region. Data can be collected for your home by using the latitude/longitude or a country code. This API uses the same data as https://app.electricitymaps.com. Not all countries/regions in the world are supported, so please consult the app to check local availability.</flag>
    <flag name="coinbase">The coinbase integration lets you access account balances and exchange rates from Coinbase.</flag>
    <flag name="color_extractor">The ColorExtractor integration.</flag>
    <flag name="comelit">The Comelit SimpleHome integration allows you to control your Comelit home automation devices.</flag>
    <flag name="comfoconnect">The comfoconnect integration lets you control Zehnder ComfoAir Q350/Q450/Q600ventilation units from Home Assistant. You need a ComfoConnect LAN Cbridge to connect the unit to your local network.</flag>
    <flag name="command_line">The Command line integration offers functionality that issues specific commands to get data or to control a device.</flag>
    <flag name="compensation">The Compensation integration and the following values as attributes: entity_id and coefficients. A single polynomial, linear by default, is fit to all data points provided.</flag>
    <flag name="concord232">The concord232 platform provides integration with GE, Interlogix (and other brands) alarm panels that support the RS-232 Automation Control Panel interface module (or have it built in). Supported panels include Concord 4.</flag>
    <flag name="control4">The Control4 integration allows you to control and monitor lights and Room Media from your local Control4 system. Your Control4 controller must be running OS 3.0+.</flag>
    <flag name="conversation">The Conversation integration allows you to converse with Home Assistant. You can either converse by pressing the microphone in the frontend (supported browsers only (no iOS)) or by calling the conversation/process action with the transcribed text.</flag>
    <flag name="cookidoo">The Cookidoo integration allows you to interact with your shopping lists of Cookidoo the official Thermomix recipe platform within Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="coolmaster">The coolmaster climate platform lets you control HVAC through CoolMasterNet.</flag>
    <flag name="cppm_tracker">This platform allows you to detect presence by looking at connected devices to Aruba Clearpass.</flag>
    <flag name="cpuspeed">The CPU Speed integration allows you to monitor the current CPU speed.</flag>
    <flag name="crownstone">The Crownstone integration allows you to control your Crownstones either via the cloud or using a Crownstone USB dongle.</flag>
    <flag name="cups">The cups sensor platform uses the open source printing system CUPS to show details about your printers, including the ink levels. It can obtain the information using a CUPS server or by communicating directly with the printer with the Internet Printing Protocol.</flag>
    <flag name="daikin">Warning</flag>
    <flag name="danfoss_air">The Danfoss Air integration allows you to access information from your Danfoss Air HRV unit.</flag>
    <flag name="datadog">The Datadog integration sends all state changes to Datadog using a Datadog Agent.</flag>
    <flag name="deako">The Deako Smart Lighting integration allows you to control your Deako devices from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="debugpy">The Remote Python debugger integration allows you to use the Visual Studio CodePython debug tooling with a remote Home Assistant instance.</flag>
    <flag name="deconz">deCONZ by dresden elektronik is a software that communicates with ConBee/RaspBee Zigbee gateways and exposes Zigbee devices that are connected to the gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="decora">Support for the Decora Bluetooth dimmer switch Leviton.</flag>
    <flag name="decora_wifi">Support for Leviton Decora Wi-Fi dimmers/switches via the MyLeviton API.</flag>
    <flag name="delijn">The delijn integration will give you the departure time of the next bus, tram or subway at a specific stop of the De Lijn public transport network in Flanders (Belgium).</flag>
    <flag name="deluge">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="denonavr">The denonavr platform allows you to control Denon Network Receivers from Home Assistant. It might be that your device is supported by the Denon platform.</flag>
    <flag name="devialet">The Devialet integration lets you control your Devialet wireless speakers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="devolo_home_control">devolo Home Control is a Z-Wave ecosystem with a Z-Wave to IP gateway in the center. The integration allows you to control devices connected to the gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="devolo_home_network">The devolo Home Network integration allows you to monitor and control your devolo PLC network. Depending on the device you add to Home Assistant, different use cases are possible. Roughly you can categorize the devices into Wi-Fi and non-Wi-Fi devices. Non-Wi-Fi devices are more or less limited in monitoring your PLC network. The Wi-Fi devices, however, can help with presence detection and remote control of your guest Wi-Fi. For details, please continue reading about the entities and look at the supported devices.</flag>
    <flag name="dexcom">The Dexcom integration allows you to view your CGM data from Dexcom in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="dhcp">The DHCP discovery integration will watch the network for DHCP requests for supported devices and services. Discovered integrations will show up in the discovered section on the integrations page in the configuration panel.</flag>
    <flag name="digital_ocean">The Digital Ocean integration allows you to access the information about your Digital Ocean droplets from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="directv">The DirecTV platform allows you to control a DirecTV receiver and its client devices.</flag>
    <flag name="discogs">The discogs integration allows you to see the current amount of records in your Discogs collection.</flag>
    <flag name="discord">The Discord service is a platform for the notify integration. This allows integrations to send messages to the user using Discord.</flag>
    <flag name="discovergy">The inexogy integration allows users to integrate their inexogy smart meters into Home Assistant.The integration is using the official REST API by inexogy.</flag>
    <flag name="dlib_face_detect">The dlib_face_detect image processing integration allows you to use the Dlib through Home Assistant. This platform enables face detection from cameras, and can fire events with attributes.</flag>
    <flag name="dlib_face_identify">The dlib_face_identify image processing integration allows you to use the Dlib through Home Assistant. This platform allow you to identify persons on camera and fire an event with identify persons.</flag>
    <flag name="dlink">The D-Link Wi-Fi Smart Plugs integration allows you to control the state of your D-Link Wi-Fi Smart Plugs.</flag>
    <flag name="dlna_dmr">The DLNA Digital Media Renderer integration allows you to control a DLNA Digital Media Renderer, such as DLNA enabled TVs or radios.</flag>
    <flag name="dlna_dms">The DLNA Digital Media Server integration allows you to browse and play media from a DLNA Digital Media Server. Configured DMS devices act as a Media Source and can be browsed in the Media panel.</flag>
    <flag name="dnsip">The DNS IP integration will expose an IP address, fetched via DNS resolution (every 2 minutes), as its value. It provides both IPv4 and IPv6 lookup as separate sensors depending on accessibility to resolvers.</flag>
    <flag name="dominos">The Dominos Pizza integration allows you to order Dominos Pizza from within your Home Assistant scripts and automations.</flag>
    <flag name="doods">The doods image processing integration allows you to detect and recognize objects in a camera image using DOODS. The state of the entity is the number of objects detected and recognized objects are listed in the summary attribute along with quantity. The matches attribute provides the confidence score for recognition and the bounding box of the object for each detection category.</flag>
    <flag name="doorbird">The DoorBird integration allows you to integrate your DoorBird device in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="dormakaba_dkey">Integrates Dormakaba dKey Bluetooth Low Energy connected locks into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="dremel_3d_printer">The Dremel 3D Printer integration allow you to monitor your Dremel 3D printer and its progress with your Home Assistant installation. This integration is currently limited to the 3D20, 3D40 and 3D45.</flag>
    <flag name="drop_connect">The DROP integration provides connectivity withDROP smart water system devices via a local MQTT API.</flag>
    <flag name="dsmr">A sensor platform for Belgian, Dutch, Luxembourg and Swedish Smart Meters which comply to DSMR (Dutch Smart Meter Requirements), also known as ‘Slimme meter’ or ‘P1 poort’. Swedish meters with a ‘HAN port’ are not supported by this integration.</flag>
    <flag name="duke_energy">The Duke Energy integration allows you to get energy information from Duke Energy.</flag>
    <flag name="dunehd">The Dune HD integration allows you to control a Dune HD media player from Home Assistant. Support is based on the official IP protocol published by Dune.</flag>
    <flag name="duotecno">The Duotecno integration can be used to control Duotecno nodes in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="dwd_weather_warnings">The Deutscher Wetterdienst Weather Warnings integration uses the Deutscher Wetterdienst (DWD) as a source for current and advance weather warnings. The configured sensor checks for data every 15 minutes.</flag>
    <flag name="dweet">The dweet integration makes it possible to transfer details collected with Home Assistant to Dweet.io and visualize them with freeboard.io. Keep in mind that your information will be public!</flag>
    <flag name="dynalite">Philips Dynalite support is integrated into Home Assistant as a hub that can drive the light, switch, and cover platforms.</flag>
    <flag name="eafm">The eafm integration offers integration with the UK Environment Agency Flood Monitoring API to provide sensors for nearby water levels. Combined with Home Assistant notifications, you could give yourself a warning if a nearby river was likely to flood your local cycle path or the only road out of your village.</flag>
    <flag name="easyenergy">The easyEnergy integration integrates the easyEnergy API platform with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ebox">Integrate your EBox account information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ebusd">Integration between the ebusd daemon (used for communication with the eBUS heating systems), and Home Assistant. The ebusd integrations uses the sensor integration.</flag>
    <flag name="ecoal_boiler">The ecoal_boiler integration is the base for pumps and sensors managed by esterownik.pl eCoal boiler controller.</flag>
    <flag name="ecobee">The ecobee integration lets you control and view sensor data from ecobee thermostats.</flag>
    <flag name="ecoforest">The Ecoforest integration allows monitoring and control of local Ecoforest fireplaces in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="econet">The EcoNet integration is consuming the information provided by a EcoNet enabled Rheem water heater or thermostat.</flag>
    <flag name="ecovacs">The ecovacs integration is the main integration to integrate Ecovacs (Deebot) vacuums and mowers. You will need your Ecovacs account information (username, password) to discover and control vacuums and mowers in your account.</flag>
    <flag name="ecowitt">Configuration To add the Ecowitt integration to your Home Assistant instance, use this My button:</flag>
    <flag name="eddystone_temperature">The eddystone_temperature sensor integration. For example Gimbal, Estimote or kontakt.io.</flag>
    <flag name="edimax">This edimax switch integration allows you to control the state of your Edimax switches.</flag>
    <flag name="edl21">The edl21 integration lets you read German EDL21 smart meters using SML from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="efergy">Integrate your Efergy meter information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="egardia">The Egardia integration enables the ability to control an Egardia/Woonveilig control panel. These alarm panels are known under different brand names across the world, including Woonveilig in the Netherlands. This was tested on the WL-1716, GATE-01, GATE-02 and GATE-03 versions of the Egardia/Woonveilig platform. Not only will you integrate your alarm control panel, supported sensors (door contacts at this moment) will be added automatically.</flag>
    <flag name="eheimdigital">The EHEIM Digital integration allows you to control your EHEIM Digital smart aquarium devices from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="electrasmart">Electra Air, is a company which manufactures and sells Air Conditioners.</flag>
    <flag name="electric_kiwi">Electric Kiwi is an independent power and broadband company in New Zealand, offering variable rates for peak, shoulder, and off-peak pricing with a selectable hour of free power.</flag>
    <flag name="elevenlabs">The ElevenLabs text-to-speech integrations adds support for ElevenLabs as text-to-speech to read a text with natural sounding voices.</flag>
    <flag name="elgato">The Elgato Lights sets the bar for high-end studiolightning. The LED lights are created and designed specifically for streamersand content creators, many of whom operate on platforms like YouTube and Twitch.</flag>
    <flag name="eliqonline">Integrate your ELIQ Online smart meter information into Home Assistant. To get an access token and the Channel ID, log in to your account.</flag>
    <flag name="elkm1">The Elk-M1 is a home security and automation controller that is capable of alarm control panel functions and automation.</flag>
    <flag name="elmax">The Elmax integration enables Home Assistant integration withELMAX control panels. Elmax panels aredomotic systems focused on intrusion detection and home surveillance.</flag>
    <flag name="elvia">The Elvia integration will import your historical grid consumption.You can use the Elvia integration, regardless of which provider you are subscribed to, as long as Elvia operates the grid. If you are unsure if this works for you, log in to Min side and check. If you see a meter there, you can use it.</flag>
    <flag name="elv">The pca switch integration allows you to control the state of your ELV PCA 301 smart switch. You need an 868 MHz interface like the JeeLink flashed with the pca-hex firmware.</flag>
    <flag name="emby">The Emby integration allows you to control a Emby multimedia system from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="emoncms">The emoncms sensor integration creates sensors for the feeds available in your local or cloud based version of Emoncms.</flag>
    <flag name="emonitor">The SiteSage Emonitor allows local power monitoring on a per circuit basis via an Emonitor device.</flag>
    <flag name="emulated_kasa">The Emulated Kasa integration emulates a TP-Link Kasa smart plug and announces the power usage of configured devices to any that might request it on the local network.</flag>
    <flag name="emulated_roku">The Emulated Roku integration integrates an emulated Roku API into Home Assistant,so remotes such as Harmony and Android apps can connect to it through Wi-Fi as if it were a Roku player.Home Assistant will see key presses and app launches as Events, which you can use as triggers for automations.Multiple Roku servers may be started if you run out of buttons by specifying multiple server entries.</flag>
    <flag name="energenie_power_sockets">The Energenie Power-Sockets integration allows you to include Energenie USB Power-Sockets into your Home Assistant setup.</flag>
    <flag name="energyzero">The EnergyZero integration integrates the EnergyZero API platform with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="enigma2">The Enigma2 integration allows you to control a Linux based set-top box which is running Enigma2 with the OpenWebif plugin installed.</flag>
    <flag name="enocean">The EnOcean standard is supported by many different vendors. There are switches and sensors of many different kinds, and typically they employ energy harvesting to get power such that no batteries are necessary.</flag>
    <flag name="enphase_envoy">The Enphase Envoy integration is used to integrate with the Enphase IQ Gateway, a communication device for Enphase solar inverters and batteries. In this documentation, as well as in integration entity names, the Enphase IQ Gateway is commonly referred to as Envoy, a name from the conception times of this integration and retained for its compact format.</flag>
    <flag name="entur_public_transport">The entur_public_transport integration gives real-time departure information for the next departures from any bus stop, car ferry quay, train station, airport and person ferries quay in Norway.</flag>
    <flag name="environment_canada">The Environment Canada integration provides meteorological data for Canadian locations from Environment and Climate Change Canada.</flag>
    <flag name="envisalink">The Envisalink integration will allow Home Assistant users who own either a DSC or Honeywell alarm panel to leverage their alarm system and its sensors to provide Home Assistant with rich information about their homes. Connectivity between Home Assistant and the alarm panel is accomplished through a device produced by Eyez On, known as the Envisalink. The Envisalink evl3 and evl4 boards provide a TCP/IP interface to the alarm panel, where it emulates an alarm keypad. This board also exposes a raw TCP/IP based API, upon which this integration is built. Currently, the Envisalink version 4 is the latest model. This integration supports both the evl3 and the evl4.</flag>
    <flag name="ephember">The ephember integration lets you control EPH Controls thermostats. The module only works if you have a Wi-Fi gateway to control your EPH system and an account on the EMBER app.</flag>
    <flag name="epic_games_store">The Epic Games Store integration integrates the Epic Games Store service into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="epion">Integrates Epion Air sensors into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="epson">The Epson integration allows you to control a Epson projector from Home Assistant.The device has to be turned on during initial configuration.When you want to add a device for the first time, turn it on before following the integration steps.</flag>
    <flag name="eq3btsmart">The eq3btsmart climate platform allows you to integrate eQ-3 Bluetooth Smart Thermostats.</flag>
    <flag name="escea">The Escea integration allows monitoring and control of local Escea fireplaces. These fireplaces are manufactured in New Zealand and sold throughout Australia and New Zealand.</flag>
    <flag name="esphome">This integration allows ESPHome devices to connect directly to Home Assistant with the native ESPHome API.</flag>
    <flag name="etherscan">The Etherscan sensor platform displays Ether and ERC-20 token balances from Etherscan.io.</flag>
    <flag name="eufylife_ble">The EufyLife integration allows you to integrate Eufy smart scales with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="eufy">The EufyHome integration is the main integration to integrate eufy devices sold under the EufyHome product line with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="everlights">EverLights are permanent Christmas lights installed on a home’s gutters or flashing. This integration can change all LEDs in a zone to a single color or activate a pattern that was previously saved to the control box.</flag>
    <flag name="evil_genius_labs">This integration allows you to control and monitor the artworks by Evil Genius Labs. Tested with the Fibonacci256.</flag>
    <flag name="evohome">The Evohome integration links Home Assistant with all non-US Honeywell Total Connect Comfort (TCC) CH/DHW systems, such as:</flag>
    <flag name="ezviz">The ezviz sensor platform uses the ezvizlife.com API to interact with the devices.It also exposes an RTSP stream, by using the local camera IPs (so the device hosting Home Assistant has to be able to access the local IP of the cameras).</flag>
    <flag name="faa_delays">The FAA Delays integration collects and displays information about delays at US Airports based on theFAA’s National Airspace System Status.</flag>
    <flag name="familyhub">The familyhub integration allows you to get images of the inside of your Samsung Family Hub refrigerator in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="fastdotcom">The fastdotcom integration uses the Fast.com web service to measure network bandwidth performance.</flag>
    <flag name="feedreader">Add an RSS/Atom feed reader that polls feeds every hour and sends new entries into the event bus.</flag>
    <flag name="ffmpeg">The FFmpeg integration allows other Home Assistant integrations to processvideo and audio streams.</flag>
    <flag name="fibaro">The Fibaro integration allows you to connect Home Assistant to a Fibaro Home Center or a Yubii Home hub so that you can control and monitor the connected devices and run scenes. Home Assistant uses a local connection to connect to the Fibaro hub.</flag>
    <flag name="fido">Integrate your Fido account information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="file">The File integration allows storing notifications in a file or setting up a sensor based on a file’s content.</flag>
    <flag name="fints">With the FinTS integration, you can fetch your account information from your bank. This only works with banks that support the FinTS (aka. HBCI) standard. The FinTS standard used by many German banks. So if you do not have a German bank account, this will most likely not work for you. To find out if your bank supports FinTS, check the bank’s website or call their hotline.</flag>
    <flag name="fireservicerota">FireServiceRota is a powerful and flexible availability, scheduling and dispatching system for firefighters.It’s the international brand of the Dutch BrandweerRooster, which is in use by more than 200 fire stations in The Netherlands.</flag>
    <flag name="firmata">Firmata can be used to add analog and digital inputs and outputs to Home Assistant. This allows for buttons, switches, motion detectors, relay control, sensors, potentiometers, dimmers, etc. The integration can currently connect to a Firmata board via serial or serial over USB.</flag>
    <flag name="fitbit">The Fitbit sensor allows you to expose data from Fitbit to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="fivem">FiveM allows players to play the game Grand Theft Auto V by Rockstar Games online with other players. FiveM adds support for custom resources. The FiveM integration lets you retrieve information from a FiveM server within Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="fixer">The fixer integration will show you the current exchange rate from Fixer.io which is using data from the European Central Bank (ECB).</flag>
    <flag name="fjaraskupan">Fjäråskupan allows you to control your Bluetooth equipped kitchen fan.</flag>
    <flag name="fleetgo">The fleetgo device tracker integration allows you to integrate your vehicles equipped with FleetGO hardware into Home Assistant. It allows you to see certain details about your vehicle, but also shows your vehicle on the map.</flag>
    <flag name="flexit_bacnet">Integrates Flexit Nordic series air handling unit into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="flick_electric">Flick Electric Co is a power company in New Zealand, based around a transparent pricing model where each component of pricing is provided. This integration uses the mobile app’s API from Flick Electric Co to get the current power price as well as each of the components price.</flag>
    <flag name="flic">The flic integration allows you to receive click events from flic smart buttons.</flag>
    <flag name="flipr">Go flipr company sells smart pool monitor and management devices. The Flipr and Flipr Hub devices publish data to the cloud via Wi-Fi and SigFox.This integration gives you also access to the Flipr Hub to control your pool equipments like pump, heater, light, etc.</flag>
    <flag name="flo">The flo integration integratesFlo by Moen smart water shutoff valves into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="flume">The Flume integration will show you the current Flume status for the given Device ID.</flag>
    <flag name="flux_led">The Magic Home integration supports several brands of switches, bulbs, and controllers that use the same protocol. Chances are high that your bulb or controller (eg. WiFi LED CONTROLLER) will work with this integration if you can control the device with the Magic Home app or the Surp Life app.</flag>
    <flag name="folder_watcher">The Folder watcher integration adds Watchdog file system monitoring.</flag>
    <flag name="foobot">The foobot sensor platform will fetch air quality data from your or yours Foobot device(s).</flag>
    <flag name="forecast_solar">The Forecast.Solar service provides solar productionforecasting for your solar panel system, based on historic averages combinedwith weather forecasting.</flag>
    <flag name="forked_daapd">The OwnTone integration allows you to control your OwnTone (previously forked-daapd) server from Home Assistant. This integration can control the OwnTone outputs (zones) with limited playback control (play/pause, previous/next track) and media info support. Playlist manipulation is not supported.</flag>
    <flag name="fortios">The FortiOS presence detection enables Home Assistant to track devices with a MAC address connected to a FortiGate from Fortinet.</flag>
    <flag name="foscam">The foscam platform allows you to watch the live stream of your Foscam IP camera in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="freebox">The freebox integration allows you to observe and control Freebox router.</flag>
    <flag name="freedompro">Freedompro, a company specialized in home automation, designs and manufactures products to make domotics affordable for everyone, installers and enthusiasts. Freedompro Products are designed to be easy to use and practical and fast to install.</flag>
    <flag name="free_mobile">The free_mobile integration uses the French mobile operator Free Mobile to send SMS to your own cell phone.</flag>
    <flag name="fritzbox_callmonitor">The fritzbox_callmonitor sensor monitors the call monitor exposed by AVM FRITZ!Box routers on TCP port 1012. It will assume the values idle, ringing, dialing or talking with the phone numbers involved contained in the state attributes.It can also access the internal phone book of the router to look up the names corresponding to the phone numbers and store them in the state attributes.</flag>
    <flag name="fritzbox">The AVM FRITZ!SmartHome integration for Home Assistant allows you to integrate AVM Smart Home (former AVM FRITZ!DECT) devices like plugs, thermostats or shutter drivers as also trigger so called smart home templates (contains settings for Smart Home devices of the same type).</flag>
    <flag name="fritz">The AVM FRITZ!Box Tools integration allows you to control your AVM FRITZ!Box router and have presence detection for connected network devices.</flag>
    <flag name="fronius">The Fronius integration polls a Fronius solar inverter or datalogger for details of a Fronius SolarNet setup and integrate it in your Home Assistant installation.</flag>
    <flag name="frontend">This offers the official frontend to control Home Assistant. This integration is enabled by default unless you’ve disabled or removed the default_config: line from your configuration.yaml file.</flag>
    <flag name="frontier_silicon">This integration provides support for Internet Radios based on the Frontier Silicon chipset. Some of the manufacturers which offer products based on these chips include: Hama, Medion, Slivercrest, Auna, Technisat, Revo, Pinnel, etc. These devices will be usually controlled by the OKTIV or UNDOK apps.</flag>
    <flag name="fujitsu_fglair">The FGLair integration provides support for Fujitsu heat pumps and air conditioners that use the FGLair app.To find out which app to use for your heat pump, check the Fujitsu FGLair FAQ.</flag>
    <flag name="fully_kiosk">Fully Kiosk Browser is a powerful kiosk browser for Android devices. It provides a number of features for monitoring and controlling your Android device. This integration gives you access to control your device and view the status in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="futurenow">The futurenow light integration allows you to use P5 FutureNow relay/dimmer units as lights. Currently supported units:</flag>
    <flag name="fyta">The FYTA integration uses the open API of FYTA to obtain the data from your plant sensors and integrate these into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="garages_amsterdam">The Garages Amsterdam integration uses an API provided by the municipality of Amsterdam, to measure the occupancy of Amsterdam parking garages in the Netherlands. You can track multiple garages by adding the integration multiple times.</flag>
    <flag name="gardena_bluetooth">The Gardena Bluetooth integration allows users to integrate their Gardena Bluetooth devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="gc100">The Global Caché GC-100 can be integrated into Home Assistant. GC-100 is a TCP-controllablehardware device which has an array of relays, RS232 serial ports, and flexible ports which can be programmed to be either digital inputs or IR blaster outputs. There are a variety of submodels of the GC-100 which have different amounts of each I/O type.</flag>
    <flag name="gdacs">The gdacs integration lets you use a GeoRSS feed provided by GDACS with information about major droughts, earthquakes, floods, tropical cyclones, tsunamis and volcanic activities worldwide.It retrieves alerts from a feed and shows information of those alerts filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location.The filter is set in the configuration as categories, radius (kilometers or miles based on unit system set in Home Assistant), latitude and longitude.</flag>
    <flag name="generic">The generic camera platform allows you to integrate any IP camera or other URL into Home Assistant. Templates can be used to generate the URLs on the fly.</flag>
    <flag name="geniushub">The geniushub integration links Home Assistant with your Genius Hub CH/DHW system, including its zones, devices, and issues.</flag>
    <flag name="geocaching">Geocaching is a real-world, outdoor adventure that is happening all the time, all around the world. To play, participants use the Geocaching app and/or a GPS device to navigate to cleverly hidden containers called geocaches.</flag>
    <flag name="geo_json_events">The GeoJSON integration lets you ingest events from GeoJSON feeds. It retrieves events from a feed and shows information of those events filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location.All entries in the GeoJSON feed must define a geometry which typically is a point or polygon with geo coordinates. In addition, this platform will look for a title key in the entry’s properties and use that as the entity’s name.</flag>
    <flag name="geonetnz_quakes">The geonetnz_quakes integration lets you use a GeoJSON feed provided byNew Zealand’s GeoNet with informationabout quakes in the New Zealand region that happened within the last 7 days.It retrieves incidents from a feed andshows information of those incidents filtered by distance to Home Assistant’slocation.</flag>
    <flag name="geonetnz_volcano">The geonetnz_volcano integration lets you use a GeoJSON feed provided byNew Zealand’s GeoNet with informationabout volcanoes in the New Zealand region.It shows information of those volcanoes filtered by distance to Home Assistant’slocation.</flag>
    <flag name="geo_rss_events">The geo_rss_events integration retrieves events from a GeoRSS feed and shows information of those events filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location and grouped by category.</flag>
    <flag name="gios">The gios integration uses the GIOŚ web service as a source for air quality data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="github">The GitHub integration allows you to monitor your favorite GitHub repositories.</flag>
    <flag name="gitlab_ci">The gitlab_ci sensor integration integrates results reported by CI/CD Pipeline Jobs in GitLab.</flag>
    <flag name="gitter">This gitter integration allows one to monitor a Gitter.im chatroom for unread messages.</flag>
    <flag name="glances">The glances integration allows you to monitor the system information provided by the Glances API. This enables one to track remote host and display their stats in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="go2rtc">go2rtc is an open source project providing a camera streaming application that supports formats such as RTSP, WebRTC, HomeKit, FFmpeg, RTMP. The go2rtc integration connects to a go2rtc instance and provides a WebRTC proxy for all your cameras. To learn more about go2rtc, refer to the project’s GitHub page.</flag>
    <flag name="goalzero">This Goal Zero Yeti integration pulls data from a Wifi-enabled Goal Zero Yeti.</flag>
    <flag name="gogogate2">The gogogate2 cover platform lets you control Gogogate2 and iSmartGate enabled garage doors and gates through Home Assistant. Device names in Home Assistant are generated based on the names defined in the GogoGate2 or iSmartGate mobile app.</flag>
    <flag name="goodwe">The GoodWe integration will poll a GoodWe solar inverter over the local network and present its runtime values as sensors in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="google_assistant_sdk">The Google Assistant SDK integration allows Home Assistant to interact with Google Assistant. If you want to use Google Assistant (for example, from your phone or Google Home device) to interact with your Home Assistant managed devices, then you want the Google Assistant integration.</flag>
    <flag name="google_cloud">The Google Cloud integration allows you to use Google Cloud Platform APIs and integrate them into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="google_drive">This integration enabled.</flag>
    <flag name="google_generative_ai_conversation">The Google Generative AI integration adds a conversation agent powered by Google Generative AI in Home Assistant. It can optionally be allowed to control Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="google_mail">The Google Mail integration allows you to connect your Google Mail to Home Assistant. The integration adds an action to allow you to set an email auto-response for when you go on vacation. A notify action is also added, allowing you to draft or send emails in plain text.</flag>
    <flag name="google">The Google Calendar integration allows you to connect your Google Calendar to Home Assistant. The integration adds calendar entities that are shown on the Calendar dashboard, and can be used for automations based on any event, or limited to specific matching criteria.</flag>
    <flag name="google_maps">The google_maps integration allows you to detect presence using the unofficial API of Google Maps Location Sharing.</flag>
    <flag name="google_photos">The Google Photos integration allows you to upload photos to your Google Photos using Home Assistant. The integration adds an action for uploading photos and amedia source to view or cast the content uploaded byHome Assistant. This integration does not give Home Assistant access to yourentire Google Photos library.</flag>
    <flag name="google_pubsub">The google_pubsub integration allows you to hook into the Home Assistant event bus and send events to Google Cloud Pub/Sub. The current free tier of GCP should allow you to sync about 1 event every 2 seconds on average (2 million invocations per month).</flag>
    <flag name="google_sheets">The Google Sheets integration allows you to connect your Google Drive to Home Assistant. The integration adds an action to allow you to append rows to a Sheets document. The idea is that you can store data on there for further processing. When you set up a config entry, your drive will have a new sheet called Home Assistant. You can then rename this to whatever you like.</flag>
    <flag name="google_tasks">The Google Tasks integration allows you to connect your Google Tasksto Home Assistant. The integration adds a to-do list entity foreach task list, allowing you to create, update, or delete items on the listfrom the To-do list dashboard.</flag>
    <flag name="google_translate">The google_translate text-to-speech platform uses the unofficial Google Translate text-to-speech engine to read a text with natural sounding voices. Contrary to what the name suggests, the integration only does text-to-speech and does not translate messages sent to it.</flag>
    <flag name="google_travel_time">The google_travel_time sensor provides travel time from the Google Distance Matrix API.</flag>
    <flag name="govee_ble">Integrates Govee BLE devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="govee_light_local">Integrates Govee lights into Home Assistant using Local API control.</flag>
    <flag name="gpsd">The gpsd integration is using the GPS information collected by gpsd and a GPS receiver.</flag>
    <flag name="gree">The Gree integration allows you to control a Gree Smart HVAC in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="greeneye_monitor">The GreenEye Monitor (GEM) integration for Home Assistant allows you to create sensors for the various data channels of the GEM. Each current transformer (CT) channel, pulse counter, and temperature sensor appears in Home Assistant as a sensor, and can be used in automations.</flag>
    <flag name="greenwave">This integration communicates with the Greenwave Reality (TCP Connected) Gateway to allow control of all lights and fixtures registered to the gateway. Bulbs and Fixtures can be created and modified inside the TCP Lighting App for Android and iOS.</flag>
    <flag name="growatt_server">This sensor is designed to gather data from Growatt inverters, offering users a choice of various alternative endpoint servers during setup. Available options include:</flag>
    <flag name="gstreamer">The gstreamer integration allows you to play audio via a gstreamer pipeline. Practically, this means you can play audio directly on the computer running Home Assistant. It is particularly suited for playing TTS. Advanced users can specify a pipeline to transform the audio stream and/or redirect it elsewhere.</flag>
    <flag name="gtfs">The gtfs integration will give you the next departure time and associated data from your public transit station/stop. The data comes from your chosen public transit authority and is formatted as General Transit Feed Specification data, commonly known as GTFS.</flag>
    <flag name="guardian">The guardian integration integratesElexa Guardian water valve controllers into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="habitica">The Habitica integration enables you to monitor your adventurer’s progress and stats from Habitica in Home Assistant and seamlessly integrates your to-do’s, daily tasks, and many more things.</flag>
    <flag name="hardware">The Hardware integration provides an API which offers information about certain board types, USB dongles, and resource usage.</flag>
    <flag name="harman_kardon_avr">The harman_kardon_avr platform allows you to control Harman Kardon Network Receivers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="harmony">The harmony integration allows you to control the state of your Harmony Hub Device.</flag>
    <flag name="hassio">Supervisor integration allows you to monitor and control Supervisor add-ons and operating system from Home Assistant.This integration is already installed if you run Home Assistant OS or Supervised. Please note that this integrationcannot be installed on Home Assistant Container or Core (Python venv) installation types.</flag>
    <flag name="hdmi_cec">The hdmi_cec integration provides actions that allow selecting the active device, powering on all devices, setting all devices to standby and creates switch entities for HDMI devices. Devices are defined in the configuration file by associating HDMI port number and a device name. Connected devices that provide further HDMI ports, such as sound-bars and AVRs are also supported. Devices are listed from the perspective of the CEC-enabled Home Assistant device. Any connected device can be listed, regardless of whether it supports CEC. Ideally the HDMI port number on your device will map correctly the CEC physical address. If it does not, use cec-client (part of the libcec package) to listen to traffic on the CEC bus and discover the correct numbers.</flag>
    <flag name="heatmiser">The heatmiser climate platform lets you control Heatmiser DT/DT-E/PRT/PRT-E thermostats from Heatmiser. The module itself is currently set up to work over a RS232 -&gt; RS485 converter, therefore it connects over IP.</flag>
    <flag name="heos">The HEOS integration is used to connect a HEOS System to Home Assistant. HEOS is a wireless audio ecosystemthat allows you to stream music to HEOS Built-in products from Denon and Marantz.</flag>
    <flag name="here_travel_time">The here_travel_time sensor provides travel time from the HERE Routing API.</flag>
    <flag name="hikvisioncam">This hikvisioncam switch integration allows you to control your motion detection setting on your Hikvision camera.</flag>
    <flag name="hikvision">The Hikvision Binary Sensor is a platform that parses the event stream of aHikvision IP Camera or NVR and presents thecamera/nvr events to Home Assistant as binary sensors with either an “off” or“on” state.</flag>
    <flag name="hisense_aehw4a1">The Hisense AEH-W4A1 is a Wi-Fi module used to give Wi-Fi connectivity to some Hisense ACs and rebranded models (Smart Cool, Beko and others).</flag>
    <flag name="hive">The Hive integration for Home Assistant allows you to interact with supported devices and services offered byhivehome.com</flag>
    <flag name="hko">The HKO integration retrieves weather data from the Hong Kong Observatory Open Data API for meteorological data in HKSAR.</flag>
    <flag name="hlk_sw16">The HLK-SW16 by Hi-Link is a simple networkable 16 port relay device.</flag>
    <flag name="holiday">The Holiday integration allows you to create a calendar of holidays in Home Assistant for powering automations.</flag>
    <flag name="homeassistant_hardware">The Home Assistant Hardware integration provides functionalityshared between Home Assistant Yellow and Home Assistant Connect ZBT-1.</flag>
    <flag name="home_connect">The Home Connect integration allows users to integrate their home appliances supporting the Home Connect standard for Bosch and Siemens using the official cloud API.</flag>
    <flag name="homee">Homee is a smart home system, able to integrate various protocols such as Z-Wave, Zigbee, EnOcean, and more. The Homee integration from your Homee in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="homekit_controller">The HomeKit Device integration allows you to connect accessories with the “Works with HomeKit” logo to Home Assistant. This integration should not be confused with the HomeKit Bridge integration, which allows you to control Home Assistant devices via HomeKit.</flag>
    <flag name="homekit">The HomeKit Bridge integration allows you to make your Home Assistant entities available in Apple HomeKit,so they can be controlled from Apple’s Home app and Siri; even if those devices do not natively support HomeKit.</flag>
    <flag name="homematicip_cloud">There is an active alert for this integration! LEARN MORE The HomematicIP integration platform is used as an interface to the cloud server. Since there is no official documentation about this API, everything was done via reverse engineering. Use at your own risk.</flag>
    <flag name="homematic">The Homematic integration provides bi-directional communication with your CCU/Homegear. It uses an XML-RPC connection to set values on devices and subscribes to receive events the devices and the CCU emit.If you are using Homegear with paired Intertechno devices, uni-directional communication is possible as well.</flag>
    <flag name="homewizard">Integration for the HomeWizard Energy platform. It can collect data locally from the HomeWizard Energy products and create them as sensors in Home Assistant. Use this integration to monitor your energy, gas and water usage to optimize your energy consumption. The information collected by this integration can be used by the Energy dashboard.</flag>
    <flag name="homeworks">Lutron is an American lighting control company. The Lutron Homeworks Series 4 &amp; 8 systems are relatively old (~2003), and use RS-232 connections to communicate with home automation systems. The homeworks integration in Home Assistant is responsible for communicating with the main controller for these systems. Communication is through an ethernet to serial converter (NPort, for example).</flag>
    <flag name="honeywell">The Honeywell integration integrates Home Assistant with US-based Honeywell Total Connect Comfort (TCC) climate systems.</flag>
    <flag name="horizon">The horizon integration allows you to control a Unitymedia Horizon HD Recorder from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="hp_ilo">The hp_ilo integration allows you to do an API call to the HP ILO (Integrated Lights-Out) sensor of your server, and use this data in Home Assistant sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="html5">The html5 notification integration enables you to receive push notifications to Chrome or Firefox, no matter where you are in the world. html5 also supports Chrome and Firefox on Android, which enables native-app-like integrations without actually needing a native app.</flag>
    <flag name="huawei_lte">The Huawei LTE router and modem integration for Home Assistant allows you to observe and control Huawei LTE devices.</flag>
    <flag name="hue">The Philips Hue integration allows you to control and monitor the lights and sensors connected to your Hue bridge.</flag>
    <flag name="huisbaasje">The EnergyFlip (formerly Huisbaasje) integration allows you to track your energy consumption collectedby the monitoring device installed on your energy meters.</flag>
    <flag name="hunterdouglas_powerview">The hunterdouglas_powerview integration allows you to integrate your Hunter Douglas PowerView devices in Home Assistant. The product is also known by the brand name Luxaflex Powerview in Europe and Australia as explained on their website, however this integration should work for both brands.</flag>
    <flag name="husqvarna_automower_ble">The Husqvarna Automower BLE integration provides connectivity with Husqvarna Automowers lawn mowers via a local Bluetooth connection. This allows connecting and controlling an Automower without any accounts, cloud, or network connection.</flag>
    <flag name="husqvarna_automower">The Husqvarna Automower integration provides connectivity with Husqvarna Automowers lawn mowers through Husqvarna’s cloud API. Only mowers with Automower® Connect or with the Automower® Connect Module are supported.</flag>
    <flag name="huum">Integrates Huum saunas into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="hvv_departures">The hvv_departures sensor will display the departures of buses, trains and ferries in Hamburg.</flag>
    <flag name="hydrawise">The hydrawise integration allows you to integrate your Hunter Hydrawise Wi-Fi irrigation controller system in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="hyperion">The Hyperion integration allows you to integrate yourHyperion into Home Assistant. Hyperion isan open source Ambilight implementation which runs on many platforms.</flag>
    <flag name="ialarm">The iAlarm integration provides connectivity with the Antifurto365 iAlarm alarm systems and has also been confirmed to work with the alarm system brands Meian and Emooluxr.Please note that the latest iAlarm-XR alarm system is not supported.</flag>
    <flag name="iammeter">IAMMETER provides both a bi-directional single-phase energy meter(WEM3080) and a bi-directional three-phase energy monitor (WEM3080T). Both of them can be integrated into Home Assistant.The WEM3050T is the latest three-phase/split-phase meter, released by IAMMETER on Nov 2023.The WEM3050T provides nearly all of the features the WEM3080T provides, with the exception of the cloud service.The WEM3050T can be integrated into Home Assistant by all of the methods that WEM3080T supports.Because there is no cloud service by default, the WEM3050T is much cheaper than the WEM3080T.</flag>
    <flag name="iaqualink">iAqualink by Jandy allows you to control your pool anytime, anywhere.</flag>
    <flag name="ibeacon">Configuration To add the iBeacon Tracker integration to your Home Assistant instance, use this My button:</flag>
    <flag name="icloud">The icloud integration allows you to detect presence using the iCloud service. iCloud allows users to track their location on iOS devices.</flag>
    <flag name="idasen_desk">The IKEA IDÅSEN integration allows you to connect your IKEA Idåsen motorized desk to Home Assistant, making it possible to control the desk height and also monitor height changes from the physical controller.</flag>
    <flag name="idteck_prox">IDTECK makes ID systems used to control access and identify users. This integration works with Proximity Readers (RFID card readers). The device is connected to Home Assistant through a serial to ethernet converter (NPort).</flag>
    <flag name="ifttt">IFTTT is a web service that allows users to create chains of simple conditional statements, so-called “Applets”. With the IFTTT integration, you can trigger applets through the “Webhooks” service (which was previously the “Maker” channel). This requires the Pro plan or higher.</flag>
    <flag name="iglo">The iglo integration allows you to integrate your iGlo Lights into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="igloohome">The igloohome integration grants Home Assistant access to paired smart access device(s). The features of this integration includes:</flag>
    <flag name="ign_sismologia">The ign_sismologia integration lets you integrate a GeoRSS feed provided by theSpanish Instituto Geográfico Nacional with informationabout seismic events like earthquakes on the Iberian Peninsula and CanaryIslands. It retrieves incidents from a feed and shows information of thoseincidents filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location.</flag>
    <flag name="ihc">IHC Controller integration for Home Assistant allows you to connect the LK IHC controller to Home Assistant. The controller is sold under other names in different countries - “ELKO Living system” in Sweden and Norway.</flag>
    <flag name="image_upload">The Image upload integration allows Home Assistant to handle image assets inHome Assistant, for example, the profile photos of your systems account.</flag>
    <flag name="imap">The IMAP integration is observing your IMAP server. It can report the number of unread emails and can send a custom event that can be used to trigger an automation. Other search criteria can be used, as shown in the example below.</flag>
    <flag name="imgw_pib">IMGW-PIB integration uses hydrological data from Institute of Meteorology and Water Management - National Research Institute to present information about rivers and water reservoirs in Poland.</flag>
    <flag name="improv_ble">The Improv via BLE integration allows connecting devices implementing Improv via BLE to Wi-Fi.</flag>
    <flag name="incomfort">This integration links Home Assistant with your Intergas gateway, including the boiler and any room thermostats attached to it.The integration uses the incomfort-client library.</flag>
    <flag name="influxdb">The influxdb integration makes it possible to transfer all state changes to an external InfluxDB database. See the official installation documentation for how to set up an InfluxDB database.</flag>
    <flag name="inkbird">Integrates INKBIRD devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="insteon">Important</flag>
    <flag name="intellifire">IntelliFire Wi-Fi fireplace modules provide app-based and Alexa control to various fireplaces. The modules do expose an unencrypted HTTP endpoint on the network that provides status information. This integration will read that URL and create a set of sensors displaying the current fireplace state.</flag>
    <flag name="intesishome">The IntesisHome climate platform lets you control IntesisHome, Airconwithme and anywAIR devices. IntesisHome provides integrations with air conditioners, including Panasonic, Daikin, Fujitsu, Toshiba, LG and more.</flag>
    <flag name="iometer">The IOmeter integration fetches data from your IOmeter device, by using the local HTTP API.</flag>
    <flag name="iotawatt">Integration for the IoTaWatt Open WiFi Electricity Monitor. Itwill collect data from the Current Transformer Clamps (Input CTs) and any Outputs that are defined on the IoTaWattand create them as sensors in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="iotty">The iotty integration lets you integrate iotty devices into Home Assistant. The iotty family includes the smart switch for lights and gates, the smart shades switch for blinds and shutters, and the smart outlet.</flag>
    <flag name="iperf3">The iperf3 sensor integration allows you to measure network bandwidth performance against a private or public Iperf3 server.</flag>
    <flag name="ipma">The ipma weather platform uses the Instituto Português do Mar e Atmosfera as a source for current and forecast meteorological data.</flag>
    <flag name="ipp">The Internet Printing Protocol (IPP) integration allows you to read current data from your networked printer that supports the Internet Printing Protocol.</flag>
    <flag name="iqvia">The iqvia sensor platform collects and displays allergy, asthma and diseaseinformation (based on a U.S. ZIP code) from IQVIA.Data measured includes:</flag>
    <flag name="irish_rail_transport">The irish_rail_transport sensor will give you the time until the next two departures (within 90 minutes) from an Irish Rail station using the RTPI information.</flag>
    <flag name="iron_os">The IronOS integration seamlessly connects Home Assistant with PINE64’s Pinecil V2 soldering irons, allowing for remote monitoring and control. This integration provides real-time updates on temperature, power, and various other settings and diagnostic information.</flag>
    <flag name="isal">zlib is a bottleneck for aiohttp, especially for WebSocket connections. Intelligent Storage Acceleration, is used for accelerating aiohttp since it can speed up compression as much as 5x.</flag>
    <flag name="iskra">The Iskra integration allows you to connect Iskra energy meters and power quality analyzers to Home Assistant. Data is polled using Modbus TCP or the Iskra Smart Gateway’s REST API.</flag>
    <flag name="islamic_prayer_times">The Islamic Prayer Times (islamic_prayer_times) integration displays the various prayer times for Muslims as sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="israel_rail">The Israel rail integration will give you the next three departure times from a given location to another one in Israel rail.</flag>
    <flag name="iss">The International Space Station (ISS) integration uses theOpen Notify APIto let you know where the station is.</flag>
    <flag name="ista_ecotrend">The ista EcoTrend integration for Home Assistant allows you to import your monthly meter readings from the ista EcoTrend service.</flag>
    <flag name="isy994">ISY is a home automation controller capable of controlling Insteon, X10, Z-Wave and Zigbee/Matter devices connected to supported hardware manufactured by Universal Devices, Inc..</flag>
    <flag name="itach">The itach remote integration allows you to control IR devices with a Global Caché iTach Device and GC-100 devices. The Global Cache IR API are similar across their product line. See API documentation links at the end of this page.</flag>
    <flag name="ituran">The Ituran integration allows you to retrieve information from your Ituran-equipped vehicle using the Ituran APP service. It pulls information from the Ituran web service regarding the vehicle’s location.</flag>
    <flag name="izone">The iZone integration allows access of control of a local iZone ducted reverse-cycle climate control devices. These are largely available in Australia.</flag>
    <flag name="jellyfin">The Jellyfin integration exposes a Jellyfin server as a media source in Home Assistant.Support is currently limited to music, movie and TV show libraries only. Other libraries will not appear in the media browser. This integration has been tested with Jellyfin server version 10.6.4 and later.</flag>
    <flag name="jewish_calendar">The Jewish Calendar (jewish_calendar) integration displays various information related to the Jewish Calendar as various sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="joaoapps_join">The joaoapps_join integration exposes actions fromJoin. In Home Assistant, the Joaoapps Join features aredivided up in two locations, the Join integration, and the Joaoapps Join notify platform.The notify platform allows us to send messages to Joaoapps Join devices, the integrationallows us to access the other special features that Joaoapps Join offers. When in doubt, you can reference the API documentation this is based on.</flag>
    <flag name="juicenet">The juicenet platform pulls data from a JuiceNet charging station equipped with a Wi-Fi connection. It will access and make available all of the devices attached to your account. It also exposes a switch allowing you to charge your car now instead of waiting for the pre-set schedule.</flag>
    <flag name="justnimbus">The JustNimbus integration queries the JustNimbus API used by the JustNimbus web dashboard.This integration allows you to collect and save data to get a historical overview of your water bagusage.</flag>
    <flag name="jvc_projector">The JVC Projector integration allows for the automation of JVC Projectors.</flag>
    <flag name="kaiterra">The kaiterra integration allows you to view the readings from your Laser Egg or Sensedge device using the Kaiterra REST API.</flag>
    <flag name="kaleidescape">The Kaleidescape integration allows for the automation of Kaleidescape movie players.</flag>
    <flag name="keba">The keba integrates your Keba charging station/BMW Wallbox into your Home Assistant instance using the UDP Smart Home Interface (manual). The fetching interval to the charging station is set to 5 seconds, same as in the official mobile app. In order to use the integration, enable the UDP Smart Home Interface by adjusting the DIP switches within the charging station according to the installation manual.</flag>
    <flag name="keenetic_ndms2">This platform offers presence detection by examining devices connected to a KeeneticRouter running NDMS firmware versions 2.05 and up. It uses telnet connection so make sure telnet is not disabled on your router.</flag>
    <flag name="kef">The kef integration allows you to control the KEF LS50 Wireless and KEF LSX speakers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="kegtron">Integrates Kegtron Smart Keg Monitor (Gen 1) devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="keyboard">The keyboard integration simulates key presses on the host machine. It currently offers the following Buttons as a Service (BaaS):</flag>
    <flag name="keyboard_remote">Receive signals from a keyboard and use it as a remote control.</flag>
    <flag name="keymitt_ble">This integration allows you to locally control a MicroBot Push (previously manufactured by Naran but now under the Keymitt brand).</flag>
    <flag name="kira">The kira integration is the main integration to integrate Keene Electronics IR over IP Kira modules with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="kiwi">The KIWI integration allows you to open your KIWI Smart Locks and Smart Entry Devices.All you need to get started is a KIWI account. Register at the KIWI website.</flag>
    <flag name="kmtronic">Integrate KMtronic devices into Home Assistant. KMtronic offers a large range of IP-connected relays that can be controlled over your local area network. This integration maps each of the relays as a separate device, enabling you to control various areas of your home (e.g. using each relay to control different garden sprinkler areas, or controlling the electrical distribution of your house from a central board).</flag>
    <flag name="knocki">The Knocki integration allows you to trigger your favorite automations simply by tapping custom patterns (such as triple taps) on ordinary surfaces.</flag>
    <flag name="knx">The KNX integration for Home Assistant allows you to connect to KNX/IP devices.</flag>
    <flag name="kodi">The kodi platform allows you to control a Kodi multimedia system from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="konnected">The konnected integration lets you connect wired sensors and switches to a Konnected Alarm Panel, or NodeMCU ESP8226 based device running the open source Konnected software. Reuse the wired sensors and siren from an old or pre-wired alarm system installation and integrate them directly into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="kostal_plenticore">The Kostal Plenticore integration allows you to get data from Kostal Plenticore solar inverters and integrate them into your Home Assistant installation. It allows you also to change some of settings values of the inverter.</flag>
    <flag name="kraken">The Kraken integration allows you to monitor exchange rates on kraken.com.For a list of tradable asset pairs check this kraken support article.</flag>
    <flag name="kulersky">This integration connects Brightech Kuler Sky floor lamps to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="kwb">The kwb integration integrates the sensors of KWB Easyfire pellet central heating units with the Comfort3 controller (https://www.kwb.net/produkte/) into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="lacrosse">The lacrosse sensor integration is using the data provided by a Jeelink USB dongle or this Arduino sketch.</flag>
    <flag name="lacrosse_view">LaCrosse View is the service provided by LaCrosse Technology that allows access to LaCrosse sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="lamarzocco">This integration interacts with La Marzocco coffee machines through calls to the La Marzocco cloud API. Optionally, local API calls, which include a WebSocket connection for (near) real-time updates and a Bluetooth connection, can be utilized for local connections.</flag>
    <flag name="lametric">LaMetric TIME is a smart clock that can be used to access applications, listen to web radio and display notifications.</flag>
    <flag name="landisgyr_heat_meter">The Landis+Gyr Heat Meter integration for Home Assistant allows you to read the meter values from Ultraheat devices by Landis &amp; Gyr. These devices are commonly used for district heating. The integration has been tested with the Landis &amp; Gyr Ultraheat 50 (UH50), type LUGCUH50. Other models are likely to work as well.</flag>
    <flag name="lastfm">The lastfm sensor platform will allow you to see whenever a user starts scrobbling, their play count, last song played, and top song played on Last.fm.</flag>
    <flag name="launch_library">The launch_library sensor will provide you with information about the next planned space launch and SpaceX Starship event.</flag>
    <flag name="laundrify">Monitor the status of your washing machine or dryer within Home Assistant using a laundrify WiFi power plug.</flag>
    <flag name="lcn">The LCN integration for Home Assistant allows you to connect to LCN hardware devices.</flag>
    <flag name="ld2410_ble">Integrates LD2410 BLE sensors from Hi-Link into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="leaone">Integrates LeaOne health devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="led_ble">Integrates multiple brands of Bluetooth Low Energy LED devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="lektrico">The Lektrico Charging Station integration integrates your Lektrico Charging Station into your Home Assistant and allows you to monitor it.</flag>
    <flag name="letpot">The LetPot integration allows you to integrate your LetPot hydroponic gardens/systems into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="lg_netcast">The lg_netcast platform allows you to control a LG Smart TV running NetCast 3.0 (LG Smart TV models released in 2012) and NetCast 4.0 (LG Smart TV models released in 2013). For the new LG WebOS TV’s use the webostv platform.</flag>
    <flag name="lg_soundbar">The lg_soundbar platform allows you to control LG Soundbars from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="lg_thinq">The LG ThinQ integration allows you to connect LG ThinQ devices to Home Assistant. The features of this integration include:</flag>
    <flag name="lidarr">The Lidarr integration pulls data from a specified Lidarr instance.</flag>
    <flag name="lifx">The LIFX integration automatically discovers LIFX lights on each network that is enabled in Home Assistant’s network configuration. Suppose any of your LIFX lights are not automatically discovered. In that case, you can add them manually using the user interface by following the configuration steps below for each light you want to add:</flag>
    <flag name="lightwave">The lightwave integration links Home Assistant with your Lightwave WiFi link for controlling Lightwave lights, switches and TRVs.</flag>
    <flag name="limitlessled">limitlessled can control your LimitlessLED lights from within Home Assistant. The lights are also known as EasyBulb, AppLight, AppLamp, MiLight, LEDme, dekolight, or iLight.</flag>
    <flag name="linear_garage_door">Warning</flag>
    <flag name="linkplay">The LinkPlay integrations for Home Assistant allows you to control various media players based on the LinkPlay protocol. The integration supports auto-discovery on your local network through Zeroconf.</flag>
    <flag name="linode">The linode integration allows you to access the information about your Linode systems from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="linux_battery">The linux_battery sensor integration is using the information stored in /sys/class/power_supply/ on your local Linux system to display details about the current state of your battery.</flag>
    <flag name="lirc">LIRC integration for Home Assistant allows you to receive signals from an infrared remote control and control actions based on the buttons you press. You can use them to set scenes or trigger any other automation.</flag>
    <flag name="litejet">LiteJet is a centralized lighting system that predates most home automation technology. All lights and wall switches are wired to a central panel. This central panel has a serial port interface that allows a computer to control the system via LiteJet’s third party protocol. Home Assistant integrates the LiteJet 3rd party protocol and allows you to get the status and control the connected lights. This integration also supports the Centralite Elegance and Centralite Jetstream.</flag>
    <flag name="litterrobot">The Litter-Robot integration allows you to monitor and control your Wi-Fi-enabled, automatic, self-cleaning litter box and pet feeders. If you have pet profiles set up, you can also track your pet’s weight.</flag>
    <flag name="livisi">The LIVISI Smart Home integration allows you to connect your LIVISI Smart Home Controller (SHC) to Home Assistant. The SHC can control compatible devices from RWE/innogy connected to it.</flag>
    <flag name="local_calendar">The Local calendar integration allows you to create a calendar of events in Home Assistant for powering automations.</flag>
    <flag name="local_todo">The Local to-do list integration allows you to create to-do lists in Home Assistant.To-do lists are shown on the To-do list dashboard for tracking items and whetheror not they have been completed.</flag>
    <flag name="london_underground">The london_underground integration will display the status of London underground lines, as well as the Overground and DLR.</flag>
    <flag name="lookin">Integrates LOOKin devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="loqed">Integrate your LOQED Touch Smart Lock with Home Assistant. The lock instantly notifies Home Assistant of a lock state change and you can change the lock state yourself.</flag>
    <flag name="luci">This is a presence detection scanner for OpenWrt using luci.</flag>
    <flag name="luftdaten">The Sensor.Communtiy integration will query the open data API of Sensor.Community to monitor air quality and other weather data from a specific (self build) sensor station.</flag>
    <flag name="lupusec">The lupusec integration allows the user to integrate their Lupusec alarm control panel and ultimately all connected sensors and other devices. For more information about the LUPUS-Electronics security system please visit their website.</flag>
    <flag name="lutron_caseta">Lutron is an American lighting control company. They have several lines of home automation devices that manage light switches, dimmers, occupancy sensors, HVAC controls, etc. The lutron_caseta integration in Home Assistant is responsible for communicating with the Lutron Caseta Smart Bridge for the Caseta product line of dimmers, switches, shades, and sensors. It will also communicate with the Lutron Radio RA2 Main Repeater for the RA2 Select product line of dimmers, switches, shades, and sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="lutron">Lutron is an American lighting control company. They have several lines of home automation devices that manage light switches/dimmers, occupancy sensors, HVAC controls, etc. The lutron integration in Home Assistant is responsible for communicating with the main hub for these systems.</flag>
    <flag name="lw12wifi">The lw12wifi light integration supports Lagute LW-12 Wifi LED controller.</flag>
    <flag name="lyric">The Honeywell Lyric integration integrates the Lyric thermostat platform into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="madvr">The madVR Envy allows for the automation and control of madVR Envy devices.</flag>
    <flag name="mailgun">To be able to receive webhooks from Mailgun, your Home Assistant instance needs to be accessible from the web and you need to have the external URL configured.</flag>
    <flag name="marytts">The marytts text-to-speech integration uses MaryTTS text-to-speech engine to read a text with natural sounding voices.</flag>
    <flag name="mastodon">The mastodon platform uses Mastodon to post status updates and get account statistics.</flag>
    <flag name="matrix">This integration allows you to send messages to matrix rooms, as well as to react to messages in matrix rooms. Reacting to commands is accomplished by firing an event when one of the configured commands is triggered.</flag>
    <flag name="matter">The Matter integration allows you to control Matter devices on your local Wi-Fi or Thread network.</flag>
    <flag name="maxcube">eQ-3 MAX! integration for Home Assistant allows you to connect eQ-3 MAX! components via the eQ-3 MAX! Cube. The components connects to the eQ-3 MAX! Cube via TCP and automatically makes all supported integrations available in Home Assistant. The name for each device is created by concatenating the MAX! room and device names.</flag>
    <flag name="mcp">The Model Context Protocol is an open protocol thatstandardizes how applications provide context to LLMs. The Model Context Protocol integrationenables using MCP Servers in Home Assistant for providing additional tools to use with aconversation agent. For example, you can add an MCP server thatsupports memory functionality, or that can search the web using functionality not alreadyavailable in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="mcp_server">The Model Context Protocol is an open protocol that standardizes how applications provide context to LLMs. The Model Context Protocol Server (MCP) integration enables using Home Assistant to provide context for MCP LLM Client Applications. For example, you can expose your Google Tasks To-do list as a tool for Claude Desktop.</flag>
    <flag name="mealie">Mealie is an open source, self-hosted recipe manager, meal planner, and shopping list. The Mealie integration will fetch and allow you to create and update data held in your Mealie instance.</flag>
    <flag name="meater">The Meater Smart Meat Thermometer integration allows for communicating with the Meater Temperature Probe from Apption Labs.</flag>
    <flag name="medcom_ble">Integrates International Medcom Bluetooth-enabled radiation monitors into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="media_extractor">The Media extractor integration gets a stream URL and sends it to a media player entity. This integration can extract entity specific streams if configured accordingly.</flag>
    <flag name="mediaroom">The mediaroom integration allows you to control a Mediaroom Set-Top Box (STB) from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="melcloud">The melcloud integration integrates Mitsubishi Electric’s MELCloud enabled devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="melissa">The melissa integration is the main integration to connect to a Melissa Climate A/C control.</flag>
    <flag name="melnor">The Melnor Bluetooth integration allows you to control your Melnor Bluetooth watering valves.The devices are set up through Bluetooth and don’t need any additional bridge or gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="message_bird">The MessageBird notification integration sends notifications as SMS messages using MessageBird to your mobile phone.</flag>
    <flag name="met_eireann">The Met Éireann integration uses the Met Éireann (The Irish Meteorological Service) Public Weather Forecast API to provide current and forecasted weather data for a given location. This integration is in no way affiliated with or endorsed by Met Éireann.</flag>
    <flag name="meteoalarm">The MeteoAlarm platform allows one to watch for weather alerts in Europe from MeteoAlarm (EUMETNET). To use this binary sensor, you need the country and the province name from MeteoAlarm. Please note that it is crucial to write the country name exactly as it appears in the URL starting with https://feeds.meteoalarm.org/feeds/meteoalarm-legacy-atom-, including any hyphens used in the name. Failure to do so may result in errors or incorrect data.</flag>
    <flag name="meteoclimatic">The Meteoclimatic integration uses the Meteoclimatic web service as a source for meteorological data for your location. The location is based on the Meteoclimatic station code (e.g., ESCAT4300000043206B) and the weather data reported is based on the capabilities of each station.</flag>
    <flag name="meteo_france">The meteo_france integration uses the meteorological data from Météo-France to provide weather forecast for any location in the world with a focus on France. One or more locations can be set via the front end or via the configuration file.</flag>
    <flag name="met">The met platform uses the Met.no web service as a source for meteorological data for your location. The weather forecast is delivered by the Norwegian Meteorological Institute and the NRK.</flag>
    <flag name="metoffice">The metoffice weather platform uses the Met Office’s DataPoint API for weather data.</flag>
    <flag name="mfi">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="microbees">The microbees integration allows you to control your microBees devices such as plugs and wall switches.To use this integration you need OAuth2 Client ID and Client Secret and your user credentials.</flag>
    <flag name="microsoft">The microsoft text-to-speech integration uses the TTS engine of the Microsoft Speech Service to read a text with natural sounding voices. This integration uses an API that is part of the Cognitive Services offering and is known as the Microsoft Speech API. For this integration to work, you need a free API key. You can use your Azure subscription to create an Azure Speech resource.</flag>
    <flag name="mikrotik">The mikrotik platform offers presence detection by looking at connected devices to a MikroTik RouterOS based router.</flag>
    <flag name="mill">Integrates Mill heater into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="minecraft_server">Minecraft is a sandbox video game developed by Mojang Studios. Minecraft servers allow players to play the game online or via a local area network with other players. The Minecraft Server integration lets you retrieve information from a Minecraft server within Home Assistant. Both Java Edition and Bedrock Edition servers are supported.</flag>
    <flag name="minio">This integration adds interaction with Minio.It also enables listening for bucket notifications: see documentation</flag>
    <flag name="moat">Integrates Moat devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="mobile_app">The Mobile App integration allows Home Assistant mobile apps to easily integrate with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="mochad">The mochad integration is the main integration to integrate all X10 platforms being controlled by mochad. Besides this integration you will have to setup your X10 devices separately.</flag>
    <flag name="modbus">modbus is a communication protocol to control PLCs (Programmable Logic Controller) and RTUs (Remote Terminal Unit).</flag>
    <flag name="modem_callerid">The modem_callerid integration uses an available modem for collecting caller ID information. It requires a Hayes AT compatible modem that supports caller ID detection (via AT+VCID=1). Usually any modem that uses a CX93001 will support this.</flag>
    <flag name="modern_forms">Modern Forms has a line of smart Wi-Fi-connected fans that allow for cloud or local control of the fan and light. There is support for individual sleep timers for the fan and light that can be set and cleared independently.</flag>
    <flag name="moehlenhoff_alpha2">The Möhlenhoff Alpha 2 integration allows you to control a Möhlenhoff Alpha 2</flag>
    <flag name="monarch_money">Monarch Money is a personal finance aggregation and budgeting service that integrates with Plaid, MX, and FinCity, the three major financial backends.</flag>
    <flag name="monoprice">The monoprice platform allows you to control Monoprice 6-Zone Amplifier using a serial connection.</flag>
    <flag name="monzo">The Monzo integration allows you to connect your Monzo bank accounts to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="mopeka">Integrates Mopeka devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="motionblinds_ble">This integration adds support for Motionblinds Bluetooth motors. Want to motorize your existing blinds? This can be done with Motionblinds motor CMD-03. Made-to-measure window coverings with Motionblinds are available through a worldwide reseller network.Beware that this integration does not work with Eve Motionblinds motors. Eve Motionblinds can be added to Home Assistant using the HomeKit Device integration or the Matter integration.</flag>
    <flag name="motion_blinds">The integration allows you to control Motionblinds from Coulisse B.V..</flag>
    <flag name="motioneye">The motionEye integration allows you to integrate yourmotionEye server into Home Assistant. motionEyeis an open source web-frontend for the motion daemon, used to centralize the managementand visualization of multiple types of cameras.</flag>
    <flag name="motionmount">The motionmount integration allows you to control the position of your TVM 7675 Pro SIGNATURE MotionMount from Vogel’s.</flag>
    <flag name="mpd">The Music Player Daemon integration allows you to control a Music Player Daemon from Home Assistant. Unfortunately, it does not allow you to manipulate the playlist (add or delete songs) or add transitions between the songs.</flag>
    <flag name="mqtt">MQTT (aka MQ Telemetry Transport) is a machine-to-machine or “Internet of Things” connectivity protocol on top of TCP/IP. It allows extremely lightweight publish/subscribe messaging transport.</flag>
    <flag name="msteams">The Microsoft Teams platform allows you to send notifications from Home Assistant to a team channel in Microsoft Teams.</flag>
    <flag name="mullvad">The Mullvad VPN integration uses the Mullvad VPN API to detect if your Home Assistant instance is connected to the Mullvad VPN service.</flag>
    <flag name="music_assistant">The Music Assistant (MA) integration allows you to connect Home Assistant to a Music Assistant Server. Once configured, all MA Players show up as Home Assistant media player entities. Media players will allow you to control media playback and see the currently playing item.</flag>
    <flag name="mutesync">The mutesync integration for Home Assistant connects to the mütesync virtual button. This tray app pairs with popular video conferencing tools such as Zoom, Google Meet, Discord, and Teams.</flag>
    <flag name="mysensors">The MySensors project combines devices like Arduino, ESP8266, Raspberry Pi, NRF24L01+ and RFM69 to build affordable sensor networks. This integration will automatically add all available devices to Home Assistant, after presentation is done. That is, you do not need to add anything to your configuration for the devices for them to be added. Go to the states section of the developer tools to find the devices that have been identified.</flag>
    <flag name="mystrom">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="mythicbeastsdns">With the mythicbeastsdns integration you can automatically update your dynamic DNS entry at Mythic Beasts.</flag>
    <flag name="myuplink">The myUplink integration lets you get information about and control heat-pump devices supporting myUplink using the official cloud API.</flag>
    <flag name="nad">The nad integration allows you to control an NAD receiver through RS232, TCP and Telnet from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="namecheapdns">With the namecheapdns integration you can automatically update your dynamic DNS entry hosted by Namecheap’s FreeDNS service.</flag>
    <flag name="nam">The Nettigo Air Monitor integration allows you to read temperature, humidity, pressure and air quality data from Nettigo Air Monitor devices. Nettigo Air Monitor is a DIY air quality monitoring system with open source firmware, based on an open hardware project.</flag>
    <flag name="nanoleaf">The Nanoleaf integration allows you to control and monitor Nanoleaf Light Panels, Canvas, Shapes, Elements, and Lines.</flag>
    <flag name="nasweb">The NASweb integration.</flag>
    <flag name="neato">There is an active alert for this integration! LEARN MORE The Neato integration allows you to control your Neato Botvac Connected Robots.</flag>
    <flag name="nederlandse_spoorwegen">This integration will provide you with time table information of the Nederlandse Spoorwegen train service in the Netherlands.</flag>
    <flag name="ness_alarm">The ness_alarm integration will allow Home Assistant users who own a Ness D8x/D16x alarm system to leverage their alarm system and its sensors to provide Home Assistant with information about their homes. Connectivity between Home Assistant and the alarm is accomplished through a IP232 module that must be connected to the alarm.</flag>
    <flag name="nest">The nest integration allows you to integrate a few supported Google Nest devices in Home Assistant. This integration uses the Smart Device Management API and Google’s Cloud Pubsub to efficiently listen for changes in device state or other events. See Supported Devices for all devices supported by the SDM API.</flag>
    <flag name="netatmo">The Netatmo integration platform is the main integration to integrate all Netatmo related platforms.</flag>
    <flag name="netdata">The netdata sensor integration allows you to display information collected by Netdata.</flag>
    <flag name="netgear_lte">The NETGEAR LTE integration for Home Assistant allows you to observe and control NETGEAR LTE modems.</flag>
    <flag name="netgear">This platform allows you to detect presence by looking at connected devices to a NETGEAR device and control the NETGEAR device.Both routers and access points can be used with this integration. Some access points will not be automatically discovered and need to be set up manually.Attached devices are only tracked on NETGEAR devices set to the router mode, otherwise, duplicate entities will occur from access points that also report the same devices.</flag>
    <flag name="netio">The netio switch integration allows you to control your Netio Netio4, Netio4 All, and Netio 230B. These are smart outlets controllable through Ethernet and/or Wi-Fi that reports consumptions (Netio4all). This integration requires Telnet to be enabled on the Netio device.</flag>
    <flag name="network">The Network configuration integration provides network configuration for integrations such as Zeroconf. It is managed by going to Settings &gt; System &gt; Network and is only available to users that have “Advanced Mode” enabled on their user profile.</flag>
    <flag name="neurio_energy">Integrate your Neurio meter information into Home Assistant. To get an API key and secret, login to your Neurio account and register an application. Note the Homepage URL and Callback URL are optional.</flag>
    <flag name="nexia">The nexia integration allows you to integrate your Nexia (Trane) thermostats or American Standard thermostats into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="nextbus">The nextbus sensor will give you the next departure time and associated data from your public transit station/stop. The data comes from NextBus, which provides real time transit data for a number of transit authorities.</flag>
    <flag name="nextcloud">The nextcloud integration pulls summary Nextcloud information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="nextdns">NextDNS is a DNS service that protects from all kinds of security threats, blocks ADS and trackers on websites and in apps, and provides a safe and supervised Internet for kids — on all devices and on all networks. The NextDNS integration allows you to monitor NextDNS statistics and control its configuration.</flag>
    <flag name="nfandroidtv">Notification integration for Notifications for Android TV and Notifications for Fire TV. You can use this integration to send notifications to your Android TV device. An overlay with the message content will appear for a configurable amount of seconds and then disappear again. Sending images (e.g., security cam) and custom icons is supported too. Icons are essentially the same as images (any image format supported by Android TV is supported), but are displayed small and to the left of the notification whereas images are large and above the notification.</flag>
    <flag name="nibe_heatpump">The Nibe Heat Pump integration allows you to control and monitor Nibe Heat Pumps in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="nice_go">The Nice G.O. integration is used to integrate with Nice/Linear and Mighty Mule products.This integration is used for garage doors and gate openers created by these companies.</flag>
    <flag name="nightscout">The Nightscout integration allows you to view your CGM data from Nightscout in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="niko_home_control">The niko_home_control integration allows you to integrate your Niko Home Control into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="nilu">The nilu air quality integration shows measurements of current air quality from NILU (Norsk Institutt for luftforskning/Norwegian Institute for Air Research) sensor stations within Norway. Makes data from the open API at luftkvalitet.info and nilu.no available in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="nina">The NINA integration displays warnings from the Bundesamt für Bevölkerungsschutz und Katastrophenhilfe in Germany.</flag>
    <flag name="nissan_leaf">The nissan_leaf integration offers integration with the NissanConnect EV cloud service. NissanConnect EV was previously known as Nissan Carwings.</flag>
    <flag name="nmap_tracker">As an alternative to the router-based device tracking, it is possible to directly scan the network for devices by using Nmap. The IP addresses to scan can be specified in any format that Nmap understands, including the network-prefix notation (192.168.1.1/24) and the range notation (192.168.1.1-255).</flag>
    <flag name="nmbs">The nmbs integration will create sensors for monitoring travel time and information between 2 stations.</flag>
    <flag name="noaa_tides">The noaa_tides sensor integration uses details from NOAA Tides and Currents to provide information about the prediction for the tides for any location in the United States.</flag>
    <flag name="nobo_hub">Integrates Nobø Ecohubinto Home Assistant. This integration is not officially supported or endorsed by Glen Dimplex Nordic AS,and the authors/maintainers are not official partners of Glen Dimplex Nordic AS.</flag>
    <flag name="nordpool">The Nord Pool integration integrates Nord Pool Group energy prices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="norway_air">The norway_air integration queries the Norway air quality data feed provided by the Norwegian Meteorological Institute.</flag>
    <flag name="notify_events">Description The Notify.Events service is an integration for the notify integration.</flag>
    <flag name="notion">The Notion integration retrieves data from Notion wirelesshome monitoring sensor kits.</flag>
    <flag name="nsw_fuel_station">The nsw_fuel_station sensor platform uses the NSW Fuel Check App data as a source for current fuel price data.</flag>
    <flag name="nsw_rural_fire_service_feed">The nsw_rural_fire_service_feed platform lets you integrate a GeoJSON feed provided by the NSW Rural Fire Service with information about bush fires, grass fires, hazard reductions and more. It retrieves incidents from a feed and shows information of those incidents filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location.</flag>
    <flag name="nuheat">The nuheat integration lets control your connected NuHeat Signature floor heating thermostats from NuHeat.</flag>
    <flag name="nuki">The Nuki integration allows you to control Nuki Smart Locks via a Nuki Bridge.</flag>
    <flag name="numato">The numato integration is the base for all related GPIO platforms of theNumato 32 Port USB GPIO expander:</flag>
    <flag name="nut">The Network UPS Tools (NUT) integration allows you to monitor and manage a UPS (battery backup) using a NUT server. It lets you view their status, receives notifications about important events, and execute commands as device actions.</flag>
    <flag name="nws">The nws platform uses the National Weather Service web API as a source for meteorological data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="nx584">The nx584 integration provides integration with GE, Caddx, Interlogix (and other brands) alarm panels that support the NX584 interface module (or have it built in). Supported panels include NX4/6/8/8E. Actual integration is done through pynx584 which is required for this to work.</flag>
    <flag name="nyt_games">The NYT Games integration fetches data about your progress on their daily puzzles.</flag>
    <flag name="nzbget">The NZBGet integration allows you to monitor and control your downloads with NZBGet from within Home Assistant. It also allows you to setup automation based on the information.</flag>
    <flag name="oasa_telematics">The oasa_telematics integration will provide you with bus and trolley arrival times for Greek public transport for Athens, using real-time data from OASA Telematics.</flag>
    <flag name="obihai">The obihai integration allows you to view the call status for your Obihai devices.</flag>
    <flag name="octoprint">OctoPrint is a web interface for your 3D printer. This is the main integration to integrate OctoPrint sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="oem">This integration supports the ESP8266 based “WiFi MQTT Relay / Thermostat” sold by OpenEnergyMonitor (archived page, no longer for sale). The underlying library only supports this single relay variant of the original device.</flag>
    <flag name="ohmconnect">The ohmconnect integration will show you the current OhmConnect status for the given OhmConnect ID.</flag>
    <flag name="ohme">The Ohme integration allows you to connect your Ohme EV charger to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ollama">The Ollama integration adds a conversation agent in Home Assistant powered by a local Ollama server.</flag>
    <flag name="ombi">The Ombi integration monitors data from your Ombi instance.</flag>
    <flag name="omnilogic">Hayward OmniLogic smart pool and spa technology control.</flag>
    <flag name="oncue">The Oncue by Kohler integration will allow you to monitor the state of your Oncue enabled Kohler generator.</flag>
    <flag name="ondilo_ico">ICO by Ondilo is a small connected device that you simply drop into the pool or spa. ICO continuously analyzes the water quality of your pool/spa and notifies you via its application. ICO provides personalized recommendations so that you use the right products in the right proportions at the right time.</flag>
    <flag name="onedrive">This integration allows you to use Microsoft OneDrive for Home Assistant Backups.</flag>
    <flag name="onewire">The Onewire integration supports sensors that use the 1-wire bus for communication.</flag>
    <flag name="onkyo">The onkyo integration allows you to control Onkyo and Integra (from 2011 onward) and also Pioneer (from 2016 onward) receivers using Home Assistant.Please be aware that you need to enable “Network Standby” for this integration to work with your hardware.</flag>
    <flag name="onvif">The ONVIF camera integration allows you to use an ONVIF Profile S conformant device in Home Assistant. This requires the ffmpeg integration to be already configured.</flag>
    <flag name="openai_conversation">The OpenAI integration adds a conversation agent powered by OpenAI in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="openerz">This openerz sensor integration uses OpenERZ API to access data from Entsorgung und Recycling Zürich (ERZ). It reports the next pickup date for the specified zip and waste type.</flag>
    <flag name="openevse">This openevse sensor integration pulls data from an OpenEVSE Charging station equipped with an ESP8266-based Wi-Fi connection.</flag>
    <flag name="openexchangerates">The Open Exchange Rates integration will show you the current exchange rate from Open Exchange Rates that provides real-time exchange rates for 170 currencies. The free account is limited to only USD as a base currency, allows 1000 requests per month, and updates every hour.</flag>
    <flag name="opengarage">The OpenGarage integration lets you control the open-source OpenGarage.io device through Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="openhome">The Linn / OpenHome integration allows you to connect an Openhome Compliant Renderer to Home Assistant such as a Linn Products Ltd HiFi streamer. It will allow you to control media playback, volume, source and see the current playing item.</flag>
    <flag name="open_meteo">The Open-Meteo integration integrates the free weather forecast fromOpen-Meteo with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="opensensemap">The opensensemap air quality integration will query the open data API of openSenseMap.org to monitor air quality sensor station.</flag>
    <flag name="opensky">The OpenSky integration allows one to track overhead flights in a given region. It uses crowd-sourced data from the OpenSky Network public API. It will also fire Home Assistant events when flights enter and exit the defined region.</flag>
    <flag name="opentherm_gw">The opentherm_gw integration is used to control the OpenTherm Gateway from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="openuv">The OpenUV integration displays UV and Ozone data from openuv.io.</flag>
    <flag name="openweathermap">The OpenWeatherMap weather integration uses OpenWeatherMap as a source for current meteorological data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="opnsense">OPNsense is an open source FreeBSD based firewalland routing platform. There is currently support for the following device typeswithin Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="opower">The Opower integration allows you to get energy information from utilities that use Opower.</flag>
    <flag name="opple">The opple light integration allows you to control the state of your Opple smart light.</flag>
    <flag name="oralb">Integrates Oral-B devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="oru">Orange and Rockland Utility is an energy provider in NY and NJ, USA.The oru sensor integration fetches your current energy usage from your ORU smart meter.</flag>
    <flag name="orvibo">Caution</flag>
    <flag name="osoenergy">The OSO Energy integration for Home Assistant allows you to interact with supported devices and services offered by OSO Energy</flag>
    <flag name="osramlightify">The osramlightify integration allows you to integrate your Osram Lightify into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="otbr">The Open Thread Border Router integration allows calling an Open Thread Border Router’s REST API from Python and via WebSocket.</flag>
    <flag name="otp">The otp integration generates One-Time Passwords according to RFC6238 that is compatible with most OTP generators available, including Google Authenticator. You can use this when building custom security solutions and want to use “rolling codes”, that change every 30 seconds.</flag>
    <flag name="ourgroceries">This integration connects with an OurGroceries account and integrates your shopping lists into Home Assistant.It adds a to-do list entity for each shopping list, allowing you to create, update, or delete items on the list from the To-do list dashboard.</flag>
    <flag name="overkiz">The Overkiz (by Somfy) IoT platform is used by many different vendors, like Somfy, Hitachi, and Atlantic. This integration will allow users to integrate their devices into Home Assistant using the Overkiz API.</flag>
    <flag name="overseerr">Overseerr is a service that allows you to manage media requests and to integrate these media requests with Plex, Radarr, and Sonarr. The Overseerr integration allows you to integrate your Overseerr instance.</flag>
    <flag name="ovo_energy">The ovo_energy integration allows you to monitor your energy consumption datain Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="owntracks">OwnTracks is a free and open source application for iOS and Android that allows you to track your location and send it directly to Home Assistant. OwnTracks can be set up via Settings &gt; Devices &amp; services.</flag>
    <flag name="p1_monitor">The P1 Monitor integration allows you to gather data from your P1 Monitor device and use it in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="palazzetti">The Palazzetti integration integrates the Palazzettistoves equipped with a Connection Box.It is accessing the device’s local API. WPalaControldevices have a compatible API and are supported by this integration too.</flag>
    <flag name="panasonic_bluray">The panasonic_bluray platform allows you to control a Panasonic Blu-Ray player. Note that the device must be on the same subnet as Home Assistant; connections from a different subnet will return an error.</flag>
    <flag name="panasonic_viera">The Panasonic Viera integration allows you to control a Panasonic Viera TV.</flag>
    <flag name="pandora">If you have a Pandora account, you can control it from Home Assistant with this media player.</flag>
    <flag name="peblar">The Peblar integration integrates your Peblar Rocksolid EV Chargerwith Home Assistant. Allowing you to monitor the charging status and energyconsumption of your electric vehicle connected to the Peblar charger, whilealso providing the ability to add the charger to your Home Assistantenergy dashboard.</flag>
    <flag name="peco">PECO is a public utility company that provides electricity to the Philadelphia metro.</flag>
    <flag name="pegel_online">This integration uses the data from the German Federal Waterways and Shipping Administration (Wasserstraßen- und Schifffahrtsverwaltung des Bundes) PEGELONLINE to provide different sensors, based on the available data of the selected measurement station.</flag>
    <flag name="pencom">Pencom Design is a manufacturer of computer-controlled relay, I/O and custom boards for commercial and industrial applications. This interface to Pencom’s Relay Control Boards is designed to work over an ethernet to serial adapter (NPort). Each switch (relay) can be turned on/off, and the state of the relay can be read.</flag>
    <flag name="permobil">The MyPermobil integration allows you to view various sensors with information about your Permobil wheelchair. For example: battery status, distance traveled, and number of seating adjustments. The values of the sensors may be delayed by several minutes and should not be relied on for any crucial applications. For the integration to work, you must ensure that voice assistant linking is activated in the MyPermobil app. To do this, open the app and navigate to Settings &gt; My Account &gt; Connection Settings.</flag>
    <flag name="pglab">The PG LAB Electronics integrations allows you to control PG LAB Electronics devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="philips_js">The philips_js platform allows you to control Philips TVs which expose the jointSPACE JSON-API.</flag>
    <flag name="picnic">The Picnic integration allows one to get information from Picnic about orders, deliveries and cart content.</flag>
    <flag name="pi_hole">The Pi-hole integration allows you to retrieve statistics and interact with aPi-hole system.</flag>
    <flag name="pilight">Pilight is a modular and open source solution to communicate with 433 MHz devices and runs on various small form factor computers. A lot of common protocols are already available.</flag>
    <flag name="ping">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="pjlink">The pjlink integration allows you to control from Home Assistant, projectors with support for the PJLink protocol.</flag>
    <flag name="plaato">This integration sets up integration with Plaato Airlock and Keg.</flag>
    <flag name="plex">The Plex integration allows you to connect Home Assistant to a Plex Media Server. Once configured, actively streaming Plex Clients show up as media players and report playback status and library sizes via sensors in Home Assistant. Media players will allow you to control media playback and see the current playing item.</flag>
    <flag name="plugwise">Plugwise provides smart home devices that allow you to monitor and control your climate, energy (including gas) consumption, and energy production. The energy information can be used for the energy dashboard.</flag>
    <flag name="plum_lightpad">Configurable/Dimmable Wi-Fi Lightswitch</flag>
    <flag name="pocketcasts">The pocketcasts sensor integration lets you monitor how many unplayed episodes you have of your favorite podcasts at Pocket Casts. This integration requires a Pocket Casts + Plus subscription to work!</flag>
    <flag name="point">The Point hub enables integration with the Minut Point.</flag>
    <flag name="poolsense">PoolSense is a smart pool monitor that publishes data to the cloud via SigFox. PoolSense eliminates the time and effort spent fixing what’s wrong with your pool water. Accurate sensors, in the PoolSense smart pool monitor, send data to a cloud server in timed intervals.</flag>
    <flag name="powerfox">The Powerfox integration allows you to gather data from your Poweropti devices, by using their cloud API and fetch the data in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="powerwall">The powerwall integration allows you to integrate your Tesla Powerwall into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="private_ble_device">Some BLE devices use a privacy feature called Resolvable Private Addresses to stop businesses from tracking you when you are out with your smart devices. Instead of having a single static address that can be used to track you, its Bluetooth address changes frequently. If you have Bluetooth enabled and functioning and know your device’s Identity Resolving Key, you can add it to Home Assistant as a Private BLE Device. We can then work out which random MAC addresses are related to the IRK and track those.</flag>
    <flag name="profiler">The Profiler integration provides a profile which is a set of statistics that identifies how much time each part of Home Assistant is taking. It can help track down a performance issue or provide insight about a misbehaving integration.</flag>
    <flag name="progettihwsw">The progettihwsw integration brings the automation experience with ProgettiHWSW boards to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="proliphix">The proliphix climate platform let you control Proliphix thermostats from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="prometheus">The prometheus integration exposes metrics in a format which Prometheus can read.</flag>
    <flag name="prosegur">Integrate Prosegur Smart Alarms into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="proxmoxve">Proxmox VE is an open-source server virtualization environment. This integration allows you to poll various data from your instance.</flag>
    <flag name="proxy">The proxy camera integration allows you to pass another camera’s output through post-processing routines and generate a new camera with the post-processed output.</flag>
    <flag name="prusalink">The PrusaLink integration allows you to monitor your Prusa 3D printer and its progress with your Home Assistant installation. This integration works with Prusa MINI/MINI+, Prusa MK3.9/MK4, Prusa XL, and with the older Raspberry Pi-based Prusa MK2.5/MK3.</flag>
    <flag name="ps4">The ps4 integration allows you to control aSony PlayStation 4 console.</flag>
    <flag name="pulseaudio_loopback">The goal behind this switch is to allow a very flexible whole home audio system based upon PulseAudio.</flag>
    <flag name="pure_energie">The Pure Energie integration integrates the Pure Energie Monitordevice with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="purpleair">PurpleAir makes sensors that measure hyper-local airquality data and share it with the public.</flag>
    <flag name="pushbullet">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="pushover">The Pushover service is a platform for the notify integration. This allows integrations to send messages to the user using Pushover.</flag>
    <flag name="pvoutput">The PVOutput integration consumes information from PVOutput which was uploaded by your solar photovoltaic (PV) system.</flag>
    <flag name="pvpc_hourly_pricing">This sensor uses the official API to get the hourly price of electricity in Spain from https://www.esios.ree.es/en/pvpc.</flag>
    <flag name="pyload">The pyLoad integration enables monitoring your downloads directly in Home Assistant. This integration provides various sensors to keep track of your download activities and allows creating automations based on the sensor information, alongside button and switch controls for performing specific tasks such as aborting downloads and managing file restarts.</flag>
    <flag name="python_script">This integration allows you to write Python scripts that are exposed as actions in Home Assistant. Each Python file created in the &lt;config&gt;/python_scripts/ folder will be exposed as an action. The content is not cached so you can easily develop: edit file, save changes, perform action. The scripts are run in a sandboxed environment. The following variables are available in the sandbox:</flag>
    <flag name="qbittorrent">The qbittorrent platform allows you to monitor your downloads with qBittorrent from within Home Assistant and setup automations based on the information.You can control the alternative speed via the Alternative speed switch.</flag>
    <flag name="qbus">The Qbus integration allows you to integrate your Qbus Control into Home Assistant. Qbus is a Belgian manufacturer of Home Automation systems.</flag>
    <flag name="qingping">Integrates Qingping devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="qld_bushfire">The qld_bushfire platform lets you integrate aGeoRSS feed containing bushfire alerts for Queensland. It retrieves alerts from a feedand shows information of those alerts filtered by distance to Home Assistant’slocation.</flag>
    <flag name="qnap">The QNAP integration allows getting various statistics from your QNAP NAS.</flag>
    <flag name="qnap_qsw">This integration interacts with the local API of QNAP QSW managed switches.</flag>
    <flag name="qrcode">The qrcode image processing integration enables QR code recognition from cameras.</flag>
    <flag name="quantum_gateway">The quantum_gateway device tracker platform offers presence detection by looking at devices connected to a Verizon Fios gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="qvr_pro">QVR Pro allows you to createan independent and expandable surveillance environment on your QNAP NAS. Theqvr_pro integration allows you to view your QVR Pro channels in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="qwikswitch">The qwikswitch integration is the main integration to integrate various QwikSwitch devices with Home Assistant. The integration requires the QSUSB Modem device and connects to the QS Mobile application.</flag>
    <flag name="rabbitair">The Rabbit Air integration lets you control your air purifier over the local network. The following device models are currently supported:</flag>
    <flag name="rachio">The rachio platform allows you to control your Rachio irrigation system.</flag>
    <flag name="radarr">This Radarr integration pulls data from a given Radarr instance.Your API key can be found in Settings &gt; General in the Radarr Web UI.</flag>
    <flag name="radio_browser">The Radio Browser integration allows you to use the directory ofradio stations collected on Radio Browserin Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="radiotherm">The radiotherm climate platform let you control a thermostat from Radio Thermostat or 3M Filtrete. Your thermostat must have the Wi-Fi module installed and connected to your network.</flag>
    <flag name="rainbird">This Rain Bird integration allows interacting with LNK WiFi module of the Rain Bird Irrigation system in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="raincloud">The raincloud integration allows you to integrate your Melnor RainCloud sprinkler system in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="rainforest_eagle">Integrate energy usage and price from the Rainforest Automation’s Eagle-200and Legacy Eagle energy gateways. The price will only be included if it is provided by the electricity meter. If you picked an electricity plan in the app, the price data will not be available.</flag>
    <flag name="rainforest_raven">The RAVEn family of devices from Rainforest Automation, Inc. includes the EMU-2, a wireless device that reads energy usage information directly from your utility meter. This integration connects to a RAVEn-compatible device attached to the Home Assistant instance via USB to integrate instantaneous power demand, accumulated usage, and current unit pricing.</flag>
    <flag name="rainmachine">The RainMachine integration is the main integration to integrate all platforms related to RainMachine smart Wi-Fi sprinkler controllers.</flag>
    <flag name="rapt_ble">Integrates RAPT Pill hydrometers into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="raspyrfm">The raspyrfm integration adds support for cheap RC 433 MHz outlets via one of the supported gateways.</flag>
    <flag name="rdw">RDW is the Netherlands Vehicle Authority. Their tasksare the licensing of vehicles and vehicle parts, supervision and enforcement,registration, information provision, and issuing documents.</flag>
    <flag name="recollect_waste">The recollect_waste integration allows you to track the next scheduled waste pickup and what type of waste from ReCollect Waste.</flag>
    <flag name="recorder">This integration is by default enabled as dependency of the history integration.</flag>
    <flag name="recswitch">The recswitch switch integration allows you to control the Ankuoo REC Switch devices.</flag>
    <flag name="reddit">The Reddit sensor integrates data from Reddit to monitor your favorite subreddits.</flag>
    <flag name="refoss">Integrate Refoss devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="rejseplanen">The rejseplanen integration will provide you with travel details for Danish public transport, using timetable data from Rejseplanen.</flag>
    <flag name="remember_the_milk">The remember_the_milk integration allows you to create tasks in Remember The Milk (RTM) from Home Assistant. You can use this if you want Home Assistant to send you a task that you should not forget, e.g., water the plants. The integration allows you to have several RTM accounts in parallel.</flag>
    <flag name="remote_rpi_gpio">The remote_rpi_gpio integration is the base for all related GPIO platforms in Home Assistant. For the platform configurations, please check their corresponding sections.</flag>
    <flag name="renault">The Renault integration offers integration with the MyRenault cloud service and provides sensors such as charger state and temperature.</flag>
    <flag name="renson">The Renson integration pulls in data from the Renson Endura delta device. Most of the sensors that can be monitored from inside the Android/iOS application can be monitored with this integration.</flag>
    <flag name="reolink">The integration allows you to control Reolink NVRs or cameras. Reolink cameras are known for their local storage, without the need for a cloud subscription or account. Reolink cameras can operate fully locally on your network, putting privacy first. When blocking internet access for the Reolink devices, the Home Assistant integration, as well as the Reolink app/client, will continue to work as usual. Reolink cameras provide excellent day- and nighttime video clarity at an affordable price. An SD card in the camera offers local recording, while an optional Reolink NVR/Hub can offer a large recording capacity indoors. As evident by the list of entities in this documentation, Reolink cameras are highly configurable and tightly integrated into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="repetier">Repetier-Server is a 3D printer/CNC server, able to control multiple devices on the same server.This integration handles the main integration to the server.</flag>
    <flag name="rest">The rest sensor platform is consuming a given endpoint which is exposed by a RESTful API of a device, an application, or a web service. The sensor has support for GET and POST requests.</flag>
    <flag name="rflink">The rflink integration supports devices that use RFLink gateway firmware, for example, the Nodo RFLink Gateway. RFLink Gateway is an Arduino Mega firmware that allows two-way communication with a multitude of RF wireless devices using cheap hardware (Arduino + transceiver).</flag>
    <flag name="rfxtrx">The RFXtrx integration supports RFXtrx devices by RFXCOM, which communicate in the frequency range of 433.92 MHz.</flag>
    <flag name="ridwell">The Ridwell integration allows users to track waste recycling pickups scheduled with Ridwell.</flag>
    <flag name="ring">The Ring integration allows you to control your Ring.com doorbell, stick up cam, chime, and intercom devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ripple">The ripple sensor integration displays Ripple wallet balances from Ripple.com.</flag>
    <flag name="risco">This integration connects with Risco Alarms, in one of two ways:</flag>
    <flag name="rituals_perfume_genie">The Rituals Perfume Genie integration allows you to control and monitor your Rituals perfume diffusers connected to your Rituals account. The integration is compatible with the first and second 2.0 versions.</flag>
    <flag name="rmvtransport">The rvmtransport integration will give you the departure time of the next bus, tram, subway or train at the next station or stop in the Rhein-Main area public transport network. Additional details such as the line number and destination are present in the attributes.</flag>
    <flag name="roborock">The Roborock integration allows you to connect your Roborock robotic vacuums to your Home Assistant. Roborock vacuums areintelligent home cleaning robots and, depending on the specific device, may have featureslike mopping capabilities, laser navigation, and options for changing cleaningperformance or location in the home. This integration enables you to control andmonitor your Roborock vacuum directly from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="rocketchat">The rocketchat notify integration allows you to send messages to your Rocket.Chat instance from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="roku">The Roku integration allows you to control a Roku media playback device. This integration only supports Roku media playback devices (such as sticks, streaming boxes, and televisions). All other smart home products (such as light bulbs and cameras) are part of a different ecosystem.</flag>
    <flag name="romy">The ROMY integration allows you to control your ROMY vacuum robot.</flag>
    <flag name="roomba">The Roomba integrations allows you to control your iRobot Roomba vacuum or iRobot Braava m-series mop.</flag>
    <flag name="roon">The Roon integration allows you to control RoonLabs music players from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="route53">With the route53 integration can you keep your AWS Route53 DNS records up to date.</flag>
    <flag name="rova">ROVA is a waste collection company that operates in the center and east of the Netherlands. This ROVA integration uses an unofficial ROVA API to allow you to get your waste collection schedule and integrate this into your Home Assistant installation.</flag>
    <flag name="rpi_power">The rpi_power integration allows you to detect bad power supply on Raspberry Pi.</flag>
    <flag name="ruckus_unleashed">This platform allows you to connect to Ruckus access points.</flag>
    <flag name="russound_rio">The Russound RIO integration allows you to control Russound devices that make use of the RIO protocol.</flag>
    <flag name="russound_rnet">The russound_rnet integration allows you to control Russound devices that make use of the RNET protocol.</flag>
    <flag name="ruuvi_gateway">Integrates Ruuvi Gateway devices aspolling BLE remote scanners via the /history endpoint.</flag>
    <flag name="ruuvitag_ble">Integrates Ruuvi’s RuuviTag BLE devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="rympro">This integration connects with a Read Your Meter Pro account to get water meter reads into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sabnzbd">The SABnzbd integration will allow you to monitor and control your downloads with SABnzbd from within Home Assistant and setup automations based on the information.</flag>
    <flag name="saj">The saj integration will poll a SAJ solar inverter and present the values as sensors in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="samsungtv">The samsungtv platform allows you to control a Samsung Smart TV.</flag>
    <flag name="sanix">The Sanix integration allows you to get water/sewage level sensor measurements from the Sanix devices made by BIT Complex.</flag>
    <flag name="satel_integra">The satel_integra integration will allow Home Assistant users who own a Satel Integra alarm panel to leverage their alarm system and its sensors to provide Home Assistant with information about their homes. Connectivity between Home Assistant and the alarm is accomplished through a ETHM extension module that must be installed in the alarm. Compatible with ETHM-1 Plus module with firmware version &gt; 2.00 (version 2.04 confirmed).</flag>
    <flag name="schlage">The Schlage integration provides connectivity with Schlage WiFi smart locks through Schlage’s cloud API.</flag>
    <flag name="schluter">The schluter integration allows you to integrate your Schluter-DITRA-HEAT-E-WiFi electric floor heating thermostat in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="scrape">The scrape sensor integration scrapes information from websites. The sensor loads an HTML page, and allows you to search and extract specific values. As this is not a fully featured web scraper like scrapy, it will work with simple web pages and it can be time-consuming to get the right section.</flag>
    <flag name="screenlogic">The Pentair ScreenLogic integration allows you to integrate your Pentair IntelliTouch or EasyTouch pool controller with Home Assistant via the Pentair ScreenLogic gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="scsgate">The SCSGate integration support the SCSGate device. This a home-brew device allows to interact with the MyHome system from BTicino/Legrande.</flag>
    <flag name="season">The season integration will provide the current astronomical or meteorological season (Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter)as a sensor.</flag>
    <flag name="sendgrid">The sendgrid notification integration sends email notifications via SendGrid, a proven cloud-based email platform.</flag>
    <flag name="sense">Integrate your Sense meter information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensibo">Integrates Sensibo devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensirion_ble">Integrates sensors talking Sensirion’s BLE protocol into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensorpro">Integrates SensorPro devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensorpush_cloud">Integrates SensorPush Cloud devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensorpush">Integrates SensorPush devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sensoterra">This integration communicates with your Sensoterra soil moisture probes using the public Sensoterra Customer API via HTTPS.</flag>
    <flag name="sentry">Important</flag>
    <flag name="senz">The SENZ integration allows you to control and monitor your nVent RAYCHEM SENZ-WIFI thermostats.</flag>
    <flag name="serial">The serial sensor integration is using the data provided by a device connected to the serial port of the system where Home Assistant is running. With ser2net and socat would it also work for sensors connected to a remote system.</flag>
    <flag name="serial_pm">Particulate matter sensors measure the amount of very small particles in the air.</flag>
    <flag name="sesame">The sesame integration allows you to control your Sesame smart locks made by CANDY HOUSE, Inc.</flag>
    <flag name="seven_segments">The seven_segments image processing integration allows you to read physical seven segments displays through Home Assistant. ssocr is used to extract the value shown on the display which is observed by a camera.</flag>
    <flag name="seventeentrack">The seventeentrack integration allows users to get package data tied to their 17track.net account. The integration creates both summary sensors, which show the number of packages in a current state (e.g., “In Transit”), as well as individual sensors for each package within the account.</flag>
    <flag name="sfr_box">The SFR Box integration offers integration with the SFR broadband router.</flag>
    <flag name="sharkiq">The sharkiq integration allows you to control your Shark IQ vacuum.</flag>
    <flag name="shelly">Integrate Shelly devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="shodan">The shodan sensor integration is displaying the total of result of aShodan query.</flag>
    <flag name="sia">The SIA Alarm Systems integration provides integration with several alarm systems that implement the SIA Protocol, including Ajax Systems. This protocol is listen-only, so does not allow you to turn on/off your alarm system, it just updates the state to reflect your alarm and allows you to act on that state, for instance turning on all lights and opening the curtains when the alarm triggers. The underlying package has support for different variants of SIA, including DC-09, DC-04 and a limited set of ADM-CID. If your alarm system uses the ADM-CID standard and it isn’t working, please log an issue here.</flag>
    <flag name="sighthound">Detect people in camera images using Sighthound Cloud. The Sighthound Developer tier (free for non-commercial use) allows 5000 images to be processed per month. If you need more processing per month you will need to sign up for a production account (i.e., a Basic or Pro account).</flag>
    <flag name="signal_messenger">The signal_messenger integration uses the Signal Messenger REST API to deliver notifications from Home Assistant to your Android or iOS device.</flag>
    <flag name="simplefin">SimpleFIN allows users to share read-only financial data. This is a paid service although it is quite affordable ($1.50 a month).</flag>
    <flag name="simplepush">The simplepush platform uses Simplepush to deliver notifications from Home Assistant to your Android and iOS device. Unlike similar apps the Simplepush app requires no registration and supports end-to-end encryption.</flag>
    <flag name="simplisafe">The simplisafe integration integrates SimpliSafe home security (V2 and V3) systems into Home Assistant. Multiple SimpliSafe accounts can be accommodated.</flag>
    <flag name="sinch">The sinch integration uses Sinch to deliver notifications from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sisyphus">The Sisyphus integration for Home Assistant allows you to observe and control your Sisyphus Kinetic Art Table.</flag>
    <flag name="skybeacon">The skybeacon sensor integration supports CR2477-powered iBeacon/eddystone sensors that come with temperature/sensor module.</flag>
    <flag name="skybell">The skybell implementation allows you to integrate your Skybell.com doorbells in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sky_hub">The sky_hub integration offers presence detection by looking at connected devices to a Sky Hub router based router.</flag>
    <flag name="sky_remote">The Sky Remote integration lets you control a Sky box using Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="slack">The slack platform allows you to deliver notifications from Home Assistant to Slack.</flag>
    <flag name="sleepiq">The SleepIQ integration lets you integrate your SleepNumber Bed via SleepIQ by SleepNumber.</flag>
    <flag name="slide_local">The Slide Local integration allows you to integrate your Slide devices in Home Assistant using the local API.</flag>
    <flag name="slide">The slide integration allows you to integrate your slide.store devices in Home Assistant using the official API.</flag>
    <flag name="slimproto">The SlimProto integration allows you to control a Squeezebox music player directly from Home Assistant, without the need for an external Media Server such as Logitech Media Server. This lets you control Squeezebox hardware like the Classic, Transporter, Duet, Boom, Radio, and Touch and software players like Squeezelite, PiCorePlayer or Max2Play. For the real DIY enthusiast, there even is a player for the ESP32.</flag>
    <flag name="sma">The SMA Solar integration will poll a SMA (US) solar inverter, energy meter or battery inverter and present the values as sensors in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="smappee">The Smappee integration will allow users to integrate their Smappee monitors, Smappee Comfort Plugs and Smappee Switches into Home Assistant using the official cloud API or the limited local option.</flag>
    <flag name="smart_meter_texas">The Smart Meter Texas integration allows Texas residents to integrate their electric meters into Home Assistant. This integration will create a sensor for each meter that shows the current reading.</flag>
    <flag name="smartthings">SmartThings is a home automation platform for connecting with Samsung or third-party devices.</flag>
    <flag name="smarttub">The smarttub integration allows you to view and control hot tubs which use the SmartTub system, in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="smarty">The smarty integration lets you control Salda Smarty ventilation units from Home Assistant. You need a MB-GATEWAY or something similar to connect to your local network.</flag>
    <flag name="smhi">The smhi integration adds support for the SMHI.se web service as a source for meteorological data for your location.</flag>
    <flag name="smlight">The SMLIGHT SLZB-06x Ethernet Zigbee coordinatorsprovide a convenient way to add Zigbee to your smart home setup.</flag>
    <flag name="sms">The sms integration allows having a local execution SMS notification via Gammu. This is ideal when the internet is offline or when the power goes out.</flag>
    <flag name="snapcast">The Snapcast integration allows you to control Snapcast from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="snmp">A lot of Wi-Fi access points and Wi-Fi routers support the Simple Network Management Protocol (SNMP). This is a standardized method for monitoring/managing network connected devices. SNMP uses a tree-like hierarchy where each node is an object. Many of these objects contain (live) lists of instances and metrics, like network interfaces, disks and Wi-Fi registrations.</flag>
    <flag name="snoo">The Snoo is a smart bassinet made by Happiest Baby that helps get your baby to sleep and helps keep them asleep.</flag>
    <flag name="snooz">Integrates SNOOZ devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="solaredge_local">The solaredge_local integration uses the local API available on some SolarEdge Inverters to allow you to get details from your SolarEdge solar power setup and integrate these into your Home Assistant installation.</flag>
    <flag name="solaredge">The SolarEdge integration allows you to get details from your SolarEdge solar power setup and integrate these in your Home Assistant installation.</flag>
    <flag name="solarlog">The Solarlog integration uses the open JSON interface on Solar-Log PV monitoring systems to get details from your Solar-Log device and integrate these into your Home Assistant installation. With the integration you may monitor the solar power production and power consumption as tracked with your Solar-Log device.</flag>
    <flag name="solax">The solax integration connects Home Assistant to Solax solar power inverters. Solax inverters may be connected to a home Wi-Fi network and expose a REST API. This integration retrieves information such as photovoltaic power production, battery levels and power, and how much power is being fed back into the grid.</flag>
    <flag name="soma">The Soma integration will allow users to integrate their Soma Smarthome devices into Home Assistant using the Soma Connect hub.</flag>
    <flag name="somfy_mylink">The Somfy MyLink integration is used as an interface to a compatible Somfy MyLink hub utilizing the Synergy API. It allows the addition of covers from the Somfy MyLink platform to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sonarr">The Sonarr integration pulls data from a given Sonarr instance. This integration only supports Sonarr v3 instances.</flag>
    <flag name="songpal">The songpal platform allows you to control Sony’s Songpal (”Audio Control API”) compatible devices such as soundbars, AV receivers and wireless speakers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sonos">The sonos integration allows you to control your Sonos wireless speakers from Home Assistant. It also works with IKEA Symfonisk speakers.</flag>
    <flag name="sony_projector">The sony_projector switch platform allows you to control the state of SDCP compatible network-connected projectors from Sony.</flag>
    <flag name="soundtouch">The Bose SoundTouch integration allows you to control your Bose SoundTouch speakers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="spc">Home Assistant has support to integrate your Vanderbilt SPC alarm panel and any connected motion, door, smoke and technical sensors.</flag>
    <flag name="speedtestdotnet">The Speedtest.net integration uses the Speedtest.net web service to measure network bandwidth performance.</flag>
    <flag name="splunk">The splunk integration makes it possible to log all state changes to an external Splunk database using Splunk’s HTTP Event Collector (HEC) feature. You can either use this alone, or with the Home Assistant for Splunk app. Since the HEC feature is new to Splunk, you will need to use at least version 6.3.</flag>
    <flag name="spotify">The Spotify media player integration lets you control your Spotifyaccount playback and browse the Spotify medialibrary from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="sql">The sql sensor integration enables you to use values from an SQL database supported by the sqlalchemy library, to populate a sensor state (and attributes).This can be used to present statistics about Home Assistant sensors if used with the recorder integration database. It can also be used with an external data source.</flag>
    <flag name="squeezebox">The Squeezebox integration allows you to control music players from the Lyrion Music Server (LMS) ecosystem. Lyrion Music Server was formerly known as Logitech Media Server.</flag>
    <flag name="srp_energy">The SRP Energy integration shows information from SRP hourly energy usage report for their customers.</flag>
    <flag name="ssdp">The ssdp “Simple Service Discovery Protocol” (part of UPnP) integration will scan the network for supported devices and services. Discovered integrations will show up in the discovered section on the integrations page in the configuration panel.</flag>
    <flag name="starline">The starline integration lets you retrieve data of your StarLine security system from the StarLine portal. You will need a working StarLine account.</flag>
    <flag name="starlingbank">The Starling Bank sensor integration allows you to monitor your account balance data as sensors in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="starlink">The Starlink integration allows you to integrate your Starlink into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="startca">Integrate your Start.ca account information into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="statsd">The statsd integration makes it possible to transfer all state changes to an external StatsD instance.</flag>
    <flag name="steamist">The Steamist will allow you to monitor the state of your Steamist steam shower and turn on and off the steam generator.</flag>
    <flag name="steam_online">The Steam integration will allow you to track the online status of public Steam accounts.</flag>
    <flag name="stiebel_eltron">The stiebel_eltron integration lets you control integral ventilation or heat pump units of STIEBEL ELTRON.</flag>
    <flag name="stookwijzer">The Stookwijzer integration queries the Atlas Leefomgeving Stookwijzer API for windspeed and air quality index. Based on these values, Stookwijzer advises people not to burn pallets or wood or use barbecues. This can help prevent health issues for people in the area.</flag>
    <flag name="streamlabswater">The StreamLabs Water integration is used to interact with StreamLabs water monitoring devices in order to retrieve usage information and manage the away mode of the device. The StreamLabs Water API is used to retrieve daily, monthly, and yearly water usage along with the current away mode.</flag>
    <flag name="stream">The stream integration provides a way to proxy live streams through Home Assistant. Most users should not need to configure anything or interface with the integration directly since it is an internal integration used by the camera integration.</flag>
    <flag name="subaru">This integration retrieves vehicle information and actuates remote services provided by Subaru STARLINK (currently only available in USA and Canada).</flag>
    <flag name="suez_water">The Suez Water integration fetches your water consumption data from the French water provider Tout Sur Mon Eau website.</flag>
    <flag name="sunweg">This is a sensor to collect information from your WEG inverters using Sun WEG server.</flag>
    <flag name="supla">The SUPLA integration allows you to use SUPLA devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="surepetcare">The Sure Petcare integration allows you to get information on your Sure Petcare Connect Pet or Cat Flap.</flag>
    <flag name="swiss_hydrological_data">The swiss_hydrological_data integration will show you details (temperature, level, and discharge) of rivers and lakes in Switzerland.</flag>
    <flag name="swiss_public_transport">The Swiss public transport integration will give you the next three departure times from a given location to another one in Switzerland.</flag>
    <flag name="switchbee">SwitchBee, is an innovation company making smart homes more accessible and affordable to any household environment.</flag>
    <flag name="switchbot_cloud">The SwitchBot Cloud integration allows you to control SwitchBot devices connected through the SwitchBot hub.</flag>
    <flag name="switchbot">The SwitchBot integration allows you to control SwitchBot devices.</flag>
    <flag name="switcher_kis">This Switcher integration allows you to control your Switcher Devices.</flag>
    <flag name="switchmate">This Switchmate switch platform allows you to control Switchmate devices.</flag>
    <flag name="syncthing">Syncthing is a continuous file synchronization program. It synchronizes files between two or more computersin real-time, safely protected from prying eyes.</flag>
    <flag name="syncthru">The Samsung SyncThru Printer platform allows Home Assistant to read current data from a local Samsung printer.</flag>
    <flag name="synology_dsm">The Synology DSM integration provides access to various statistics from your Synology NAS (DSM 5.x and higher), as well as cameras from the Surveillance Station and will allow to use the File Station as a backup location.</flag>
    <flag name="synology_srm">This integration allows you to detect presence by looking at connected devices to a Synology SRM router.</flag>
    <flag name="system_bridge">System Bridge is an application that runs on your local machine to share system information via its API/WebSocket. You can also send commands to the device such as opening a URL or sending keyboard keypresses.</flag>
    <flag name="systemmonitor">The System monitor integration allows you to monitor disk usage, memory usage, network usage, CPU usage, and running processes.</flag>
    <flag name="tado">The Tado integration platform is used as an interface to the my.tado.com website.</flag>
    <flag name="tailscale">The Tailscale integration integrates the Tailscale APIwith Home Assistant; giving you the possibility to monitor and automate onthe state of the devices in your Tailscale VPN network (Tailnet).</flag>
    <flag name="tailwind">The Tailwind integration integrates Tailwindgarage door controllers fully locally.</flag>
    <flag name="tami4">The Tami4 Edge integration allows you to control and monitor Tami4 Edge / Edge+ by Strauss devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tankerkoenig">The tankerkoenig platform allows you to monitor the fuel prices with tankerkoenig.de from within Home Assistant and setup automations based on the information.To use this sensor you need an API key from tankerkoenig. Go to tankerkoenig API and click on API-KEY in the top right, fill out the form and request a key. The API is free, but requests should be limited to less than once every 5 minutes.</flag>
    <flag name="tank_utility">Add Tank Utility propane tank monitors to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tapsaff">The tapsaff binary sensor integration provides the ‘Taps Aff’ status for a given location within the UK using Taps Aff.</flag>
    <flag name="tasmota">This integration allows you to control Tasmota devices over MQTT.</flag>
    <flag name="tautulli">The Tautulli integration will monitor activity on a given Tautulli Server. It will create a sensor that shows the number of currently active streams as the state. If you click the sensor for more details, it will show you more statistics.</flag>
    <flag name="technove">The TechnoVE integration provides connectivity with TechnoVE Smart Charging Station through the station local API.</flag>
    <flag name="ted5000">The ted 5000 monitors electricity consumption/production by connecting to the TED gateway, itself connected to one or several Measuring Transmitting Units (MTU). The platform creates up to two sensors per MTU, one for Wattage the other for Voltage.</flag>
    <flag name="tedee">This integration interacts with your Tedee locks by communicating with the Tedee bridge through HTTP. The integration will communicate with your lock locally.</flag>
    <flag name="telegram_bot">Use Telegram on your mobile or desktop device to send and receive messages or commands to/from your Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tellduslive">The tellduslive integration let you connect to the Telldus Live API. It’s cloud platform that connects to your Tellstick Net or Tellstick ZNet connected gear at home.</flag>
    <flag name="tellstick">The tellstick integration integrates TellStick devices into Home Assistant. This integration allows users to add switches, lights, and sensors which are communicating with 433 MHz. There are a number of vendors (Capidi Elro, Intertechno, Nexa, Proove, Sartano, and Viking) who are selling products that work with TellStick. For more details, please check the TellStick protocol list.</flag>
    <flag name="temper">This temper sensor integration allows you to get the current temperature from a TEMPer device.</flag>
    <flag name="tensorflow">The TensorFlow image processing integration allows you to detect and recognize objects in a camera image using TensorFlow. The state of the entity is the number of objects detected, and recognized objects are listed in the summary attribute along with quantity. The matches attribute provides the confidence score for recognition and the bounding box of the object for each detection category.</flag>
    <flag name="tesla_fleet">There is an active alert for this integration! LEARN MORE The Tesla Fleet API integration exposes various sensors from Tesla vehicles and energy sites using the Tesla Fleet API.</flag>
    <flag name="tesla_wall_connector">The Tesla Wall Connector integration allows you to integrate your Gen 3 Tesla Wall Connector with Wi-Fi into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="teslemetry">The Teslemetry integration exposes various commands and sensors from the Tesla vehicles and energy sites connected to a Teslemetry subscription.</flag>
    <flag name="tessie">The Tessie integration exposes various commands and sensors from the Tesla vehicles and energy products connected to your Tessie subscription.</flag>
    <flag name="thermobeacon">Integrates ThermoBeacon devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="thermopro">Integrates ThermoPro devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="thethingsnetwork">The thethingsnetwork integration allows you to interact with the The Things Network from within Home Assistant. This community-driven and open network supports LoRaWAN for long-range (~5 to 15 km) communication with low bandwidth (51 bytes/message). Gateways transfer the received data from the sensors to The Things Network.</flag>
    <flag name="thingspeak">The thingspeak integrations makes Home Assistant communicate with the ThingSpeak API.For now, it records exactly one entity at once, which is great for testing purposes. For long-time storage you should rely on the InfluxDB integration.</flag>
    <flag name="thinkingcleaner">There is currently support for the following device types within Home Assistant:</flag>
    <flag name="thread">The Thread integration helps you track the different Thread networks in your home and store the Thread network credentials (similar to a Wi-Fi password). The Thread integration in Home Assistant is currently still a work in progress.</flag>
    <flag name="tibber">The tibber integration provides a sensor with the current electricity price if you are a Tibber customer.If you have a Tibber Pulse or Watty it will also show the electricity consumption in real-time. You get a sensor for monthly consumption, monthly cost, and monthly peak hour. If you do have a real-time meter it is updated once every hour, otherwise it is updated once per day. Statistics with hourly consumption and cost data is generated that can be used in the Energy Dashboard (the ids are tibber:energy_consumption_HOMEID and tibber:energy_totalcost_HOMEID). If you produce energy there are also statistics with hourly production and profit data generated which can also be used there (the ids are tibber:energy_production_HOMEID and tibber:energy_profit_HOMEID).</flag>
    <flag name="tikteck">Support for the Bluetooth smart bulb from Tikteck. To enable these lights, add the following lines to your configuration.yaml file:</flag>
    <flag name="tile">The tile platform allows Home Assistant to utilize Tile® Bluetooth trackers.The official Tile mobile app handles the actual tracking of Tile devices usingthe mobile device’s Bluetooth and GPS.</flag>
    <flag name="tilt_ble">Integrates Tilt Hydrometer BLE devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tmb">This sensor will provide you the remaining time, in minutes, for the next bus in a specific stop by using the iBus service.</flag>
    <flag name="todoist">This platform allows you to connect to your Todoist projects as todo or calendar entities. All tasks get updated roughly every 15 minutes.</flag>
    <flag name="tolo">The TOLO integration allows to control Steamtec TOLO devices with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tomorrowio">The Tomorrow.io integration allows you to obtain weather, air quality, pollen, and fire information from the Tomorrow.io API.</flag>
    <flag name="toon">The Toon integration platform can be used to control your Quby Toon thermostat,which is currently being sold as:</flag>
    <flag name="totalconnect">The totalconnect integration provides connectivity with Resideo Total Connect 2.0-enabled alarm systems.</flag>
    <flag name="touchline">The touchline climate platform let you control ROTH Touchline floor heating thermostats from Roth.</flag>
    <flag name="touchline_sl">The Roth Touchline SL climate integration enables you to control Roth Touchline SL underfloor heating systems.</flag>
    <flag name="tplink_lte">The TP-Link LTE integration for Home Assistant makes it possible to send SMS’s from the TP-Link LTE router. Phone numbers have to be pre-defined as part of the YAML configuration, and each phone number will turn up as additional notify action in Home Assistant. The integration adds a new notify action for each adds a notification action to Home Assistant that can be used to send SMSs provides a notification action that will send an SMS. Tested only with TL-MR6400 v4.</flag>
    <flag name="tplink">The tplink integration allows you to control your TP-Link Kasa Smart Home Devices and TP-Link Tapo Devices such as cameras, doorbells, chimes, lights, plugs, wall switches, robot vacuums, hubs, and hub-attached devices.</flag>
    <flag name="tplink_omada">The TP-Link Omada SDN Controller integration allows you to control your TP-Link Omada SDN Devices such as network switches, access points, and internet gateways. It requires a local Omada controller (software or hardware controllers) and does not currently support the paid-for TP-Link Omada Cloud Management SAAS Platform.</flag>
    <flag name="traccar">Traccar uses GPS for tracking and has support for over 1500 different types of devices. You can use the Traccar Client app on a smartphone via webhook.</flag>
    <flag name="traccar_server">Traccar uses GPS for tracking and has support for over 1500 different types of devices. You can use the Traccar Server integration to communicate with your own Traccar Server, which is also available as Home Assistant add-on.</flag>
    <flag name="tractive">Tractive is an Austrian company that develops real-time location trackers for pets and other animals using GPS and GSM technology.</flag>
    <flag name="tradfri">The IKEA TRÅDFRI integration allows you to connect your IKEA Trådfri Gateway to Home Assistant. The gateway can control compatible Zigbee-based lights (certified Zigbee Light Link products) connected to it.</flag>
    <flag name="trafikverket_camera">Retrieve camera feed from Trafikverket.</flag>
    <flag name="trafikverket_ferry">Retrieve ferry departure information from Trafikverket.</flag>
    <flag name="trafikverket_train">Retrieve train departure information from Trafikverket.</flag>
    <flag name="trafikverket_weatherstation">Showing weather information provided by Trafikverket weather stations in Sweden.</flag>
    <flag name="transmission">The Transmission integration allows you to monitor your Transmission BitTorrent downloads from within Home Assistant and set up automations based on that information.</flag>
    <flag name="transport_nsw">The transport_nsw sensor will give you the time until the next departure from a Transport NSW stop for bus, train, light rail or ferry.</flag>
    <flag name="travisci">With this sensor platform, you will be able to integrate the test build results reported by Travis-CI working within Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="trend">The trend platform allows you to create sensors which show the trend ofnumeric state orstate_attributes from other entities. This sensor requiresat least two updates of the underlying sensor to establish a trend.Thus it can take some time to show an accurate state. It can be usefulas part of automations, where you want to base an action on a trend.</flag>
    <flag name="triggercmd">The TRIGGERcmd integration allows you to run commands on computers via TRIGGERcmd with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="tts">Text-to-speech (TTS) enables Home Assistant to speak to you.</flag>
    <flag name="tuya">The Tuya integration integrates all Powered by Tuya devices you have added to the Tuya Smart and Tuya Smart Life apps.</flag>
    <flag name="twentemilieu">The Twente Milieu integration enables you to monitor the upcomingwaste collection schedules provided byTwente Milieu for various waste categories.This integration helps you stay informed about the next pickup dates fordifferent types of waste, ensuring you never miss a collection day.</flag>
    <flag name="twilio">The twilio integration enables the sending of notifications via SMS and the creation of calls with Twilio.</flag>
    <flag name="twinkly">The Twinkly integration allows you to control Twinkly LED string from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="twitch">The Twitch integration will allow you to monitor Twitch channel status from within Home Assistant and setup automation based on the information.</flag>
    <flag name="twitter">The twitter notification platform uses X to deliver notifications from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ubus">This is a presence detection scanner for OpenWrt using ubus. It scans for changes in hostapd.*, which will detect and report changes in devices connected to the access point on the router.</flag>
    <flag name="ukraine_alarm">The Ukraine Alarm integration will create 6 binary sensors for your selected region in Ukraine:</flag>
    <flag name="unifi_direct">This integration allows you to detect presence by looking at devices connected to a UniFi AP. This device tracker differs from Ubiquiti UniFi because it doesn’t require the UniFi Network application.</flag>
    <flag name="unifiled">UniFi LED by Ubiquiti Networks, inc. is a system of controller managed LED light panels and dimmers.</flag>
    <flag name="unifi">UniFi Network by Ubiquiti Networks, inc. is a software that binds gateways, switches and wireless access points together with one graphical front end.</flag>
    <flag name="unifiprotect">The UniFi Protect integration adds support for retrieving camera feeds and sensor data from a UniFi Protect application by Ubiquiti Networks, inc. that is running on a UniFi OS Console.</flag>
    <flag name="upb">The *Universal Powerline Bus (UPB) integration allows Home Assistant to connect to a Universal Powerline Bus Powerline Interface Module (UPB PIM) to get status and control UPB devices and UPB links. The UPB PIM may be connected either to a serial port or over TCP. The integration implements the following platforms:</flag>
    <flag name="upc_connect">The upc_connect integration offers presence detection by looking at connected devices to a Connect Box from Liberty Global (also known as UPC Cablecom in Switzerland) which is an Internet provider in Switzerland, Austria, the Netherlands (under Ziggo) and Hungary (under Vodafone).</flag>
    <flag name="upcloud">The UpCloud integration allows you to access the information about your UpCloud servers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="upnp">The UPnP/IGD integration enables you to collect network statistics from your router such as bytes in/out and packets in/out, uptime, WAN IP address, and WAN connectivity status. This information is provided by the UPnP/Internet Gateway Device (IGD) Protocol if enabled on your router.</flag>
    <flag name="uptimerobot">The UptimeRobot integration provides entities to get the status for all of your monitors from your account on UptimeRobot.</flag>
    <flag name="usb">The USB Discovery integration will detect newly connected USB devices. Discovered devices will show up in the discovered section on the integrations page in the configuration panel.</flag>
    <flag name="usgs_earthquakes_feed">The usgs_earthquakes_feed platform lets you integrate a GeoJSON feed provided by the U.S. Geological Survey with information about seismic events like earthquakes. It retrieves incidents from a feed and shows information of those incidents filtered by distance to Home Assistant’s location.</flag>
    <flag name="utility_meter">The Utility Meter integration provides functionality to track consumptions of various utilities (e.g., energy, gas, water, heating).</flag>
    <flag name="uvc">The uvc camera integration allows you to integrate UniFi Video Camera (UVC) into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="v2c">The V2C integration allows monitoring and control of a local V2C Trydan EVSE in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="vallox">The Vallox integration lets you control any Vallox ventilation unit that is supported by the vallox_websocket_api (follow the link for a list of supported units).</flag>
    <flag name="vasttrafik">The vasttrafik integration will provide you traveling details for the larger Göteborg area in Sweden from the Västtrafik public transportation service.</flag>
    <flag name="velbus">The Velbus integration is used to control Velbus modules. It supports the Velbus USB, Velbus serial and a TCP/IP gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="velux">Velux integration for Home Assistant allows you to connect to a Velux KLF 200 interface, to control io-homecontrol devices like windows and blinds. The module allows you to start scenes configured within KLF 200.</flag>
    <flag name="venstar">The Venstar climate integration allows you to control Venstar thermostats from Home Assistant.Venstar thermostats feature a local API that allows for automation without the need for their Skyport cloud service.</flag>
    <flag name="vera">The Vera hub is a controller mainly for connecting to Z-Wave devices.</flag>
    <flag name="verisure">Home Assistant has support to integrate your Verisure devices.</flag>
    <flag name="versasense">The VersaSense integration supports the VersaSense Edge Gateway. The gateway is able to control hubs and their peripherals (sensors and actuators) in the mesh network.</flag>
    <flag name="version">The Version integration can display the current Home Assistant Core versions.</flag>
    <flag name="vesync">The VeSync integration enables you to control smart switches and outlets connected to the VeSync App.</flag>
    <flag name="vicare">The Viessmann ViCare integration lets you control Viessmann devices via the Viessmann ViCare (REST) API.Most recent network-connected Viessmann heating devices (e.g., gas boilers) should be supported.</flag>
    <flag name="vilfo">The Vilfo Router integration allows you to observe the state of your Vilfo Router from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="vivotek">The VIVOTEK camera integration allows you to integrate a VIVOTEK IP camera into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="vizio">The VIZIO SmartCast integration allows you to control SmartCast-compatible TVs and sound bars (2016+ models).</flag>
    <flag name="vlc">The vlc platform allows you to control VLC media player.</flag>
    <flag name="vlc_telnet">The VLC media player via Telnet integration allows you to control a VLC media player using the built in telnet interface.</flag>
    <flag name="vodafone_station">The Vodafone Station integration allows you to control your Vodafone Station based router.</flag>
    <flag name="voip">The VoIP integration enables users to talk to Assist using an analog phone and a VoIP adapter. Currently, the system works with the Grandstream HT801. See the tutorial for detailed instructions.</flag>
    <flag name="volkszaehler">The Volkszaehler integration is consuming the system information provided by the Volkszaehler API.</flag>
    <flag name="volumio">The Volumio integration allows you to control a Volumio media player from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="volvooncall">The Volvo On Call integration offers integration with the Volvo Cars App (former Volvo On Call) cloud service and offers presence detection as well as sensors such as odometer and fuel level.</flag>
    <flag name="vulcan">The Uonet+ Vulcan integration allows you to view timetable from your e-register.</flag>
    <flag name="vultr">The Vultr integration allows you to access information about and interact with your Vultr subscriptions (Virtual Private Servers) from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="w800rf32">The WGL Designs W800RF32 integration supports W800RF32 devices by WGL Designs whichcommunicate in the frequency range of 310MHz or if you are outside Canada or the U.S., 433.92 MHz.</flag>
    <flag name="wake_on_lan">The Wake on LAN integration enables the ability to send magic packets to Wake on LAN capable devices to turn them on.</flag>
    <flag name="wallbox">The Wallbox integration pulls data from the MyWallbox Portal for your Wallbox charging station.</flag>
    <flag name="waqi">The World Air Quality Index (WAQI) integration will query World Air Quality Index service to check AQI value for a specific set of locations. The resulting indexes will be added to the Home Assistant as sensor outputs.</flag>
    <flag name="waterfurnace">The WaterFurnace integration communicates with the WaterFurnace Symphony website’s WebSocket to show you many of the sensors in your system. While not an official API, this is the same backend the Symphony website is based on, and should be reasonably stable.</flag>
    <flag name="watergate">The Watergate integration integrates your Watergate Devices (currently Sonic Wi-Fi) with your Home Assistant.With this integration, you are able to:</flag>
    <flag name="watson_iot">The IBM Watson IoT Platform integration enables you to link the devices in Home Assistantwith an IBM Watson IoT Platform instance.</flag>
    <flag name="watttime">The WattTime integration allows users to get real-time emissions data for a latitude/longitude from WattTime.</flag>
    <flag name="waze_travel_time">The Waze Travel Time integration provides travel time from the Waze.</flag>
    <flag name="weatherflow_cloud">The WeatherFlow Cloud integration provides access to cloud provided Weather Forecast of a user’s Tempest Weather Stations. In order to access the station, you will need to configure the integration with an Api Key.</flag>
    <flag name="weatherflow">The WeatherFlow integration that reads weather data from all WeatherFlow Tempest compatible weather station on the local network.</flag>
    <flag name="weatherkit">The Apple WeatherKit integration obtains current weather and forecasts (hourly and daily) from Apple Weather. It is the most direct replacement for those coming from the Dark Sky API since Apple bought Dark Sky and implemented its technology into their weather service.</flag>
    <flag name="webdav">This integration allows you to use a WebDAV compatible location for Home Assistant Backups.</flag>
    <flag name="webmin">Webmin is a web-based interface for the system administration of Unix-like servers.</flag>
    <flag name="webostv">The webostv platform allows you to control a LG webOS TV.</flag>
    <flag name="weheat">The Weheat integration allows you to display your Weheat devices through Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="wemo">The Belkin WeMo integration to integrate various Belkin WeMo devices with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="whirlpool">The Whirlpool Appliances integration integrates Whirlpool 6th Sense Live, and Whirlpool/Maytag Washer and Dryer appliances into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="whois">The Whois integration allows you to perform daily WHOIS lookups against your owned domains. This provides you with information such as expiration_date, name_servers and registrar details.</flag>
    <flag name="wiffi">This Wiffi integration allows you to connect your STALL WIFFI devices directly to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="wilight">The WiLight integration is to integrate WiLight devices with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="wirelesstag">The Wireless Sensor Tags integration allows you to integrate your wirelesstag.net sensors tags in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="withings">The Withings integration consumes data from various health products produced by Withings.</flag>
    <flag name="wiz">The WiZ integration allows you to control your WiZ lights and smart sockets.The devices are set up through your Wi-Fi network and don’t need any additional bridge or gateway.</flag>
    <flag name="wled">WLED is a fast and feature-richimplementation of an ESP8266/ESP32 webserver to control NeoPixel LEDs(like WS2812B, WS2811, SK6812, and similar) and SPI based chipsets(like WS2801 and APA102).</flag>
    <flag name="wmspro">The WMS WebControl pro integration allows you to integrate WAREMA devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="wolflink">The Wolf SmartSet Service integration uses the Wolf Smart-Set web service as a source to fetch your heating system status.</flag>
    <flag name="workday">The workday binary sensor indicates whether the current day is a workday or not.</flag>
    <flag name="ws66i">The Soundavo WS66i 6-Zone Amplifier integration allows you to control the Soundavo Whole-Home Audio Amplifier via the local network. This amplifier is an upgrade of the amplifier sold by Monoprice that adds 2 built-in wireless streamers and an Ethernet port for control over LAN.</flag>
    <flag name="wyoming">The Wyoming integration connects external voice services to Home Assistant using a small protocol. This enables Assist to use a variety of local speech-to-text, text-to-speech, and wake-word-detection systems, such as:</flag>
    <flag name="xbox">The Xbox integration allows you to control Xbox One (or newer) consoles from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="xeoma">The Xeoma camera integration allows you to view the video feeds from a Xeoma video surveillance server.</flag>
    <flag name="xiaomi_aqara">The Xiaomi Gateway (Aqara) integration allows you to integrate Xiaomi Aqara-compatible devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="xiaomi_ble">Integrates devices that use the Xiaomi Mijia BLE MiBeacon protocol and the BLE protocols implemented in the MiScales and the MiFora plant sensor. This integration does not support Xiaomi BLE Mesh devices. The integration listens to Bluetooth broadcasts that the device makes by itself, allowing it to track the latest sensor values or events without waking the device up for polling (except HHCCJCY01, see note below). This method conserves battery lifetime.</flag>
    <flag name="xiaomi_miio">The Xiaomi Miio integration supports the following devices:</flag>
    <flag name="xiaomi_tv">The xiaomi_tv integration allows you to control a Xiaomi TV.The Xiaomi TV integration only supports Xiaomi TVs running MIUI.</flag>
    <flag name="xmpp">The xmpp notification integration allows you to deliver notifications from Home Assistant to a Jabber (XMPP) account.</flag>
    <flag name="xs1">The EZcontrol XS1 integration for Home Assistant allows you to observe and control devices configured on the XS1 Gateway. Please have a look at the official documentation for using this gateway Bedienungsanleitung v3.0.0.0.</flag>
    <flag name="yale">The Yale integration allows you to integrate your Yale devices in Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yale_smart_alarm">The Yale Smart Living integration provides connectivity with the Yale Smart Alarm systems and Smart Hub through Yale’s API.</flag>
    <flag name="yalexs_ble">Integrates Yale Access Bluetooth devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yamaha">The yamaha integration allows you to control Yamaha Network Receivers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yamaha_musiccast">The Yamaha MusicCast integration allows you to control Yamaha MusicCast Receivers from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yandex_transport">The yandex_tranport integration uses Yandex Maps it will give you the time until the next departure time from a bus/tramway/etc stop.</flag>
    <flag name="yardian">The Yardian integration allows you to control your Yardian Smart Sprinkler Controller.</flag>
    <flag name="yeelight">The Yeelight integration allows you to control your Yeelight Wi-Fi bulbs with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yeelightsunflower">The yeelightsunflower integration allows you to control your Yeelight Sunflower light bulbs with Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="yi">The yi camera platform allows you to utilize Yi Home Cameras within Home Assistant. Specifically, this platform supports the line of Yi Home Cameras that are based on the Hi3518e Chipset. This includes:</flag>
    <flag name="yolink">Integrates YoLink Devices into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="youless">The YouLess integration for Home Assistant allows you to read the meter values from sensors created by YouLess.</flag>
    <flag name="youtube">The YouTube integration allows you to connect YouTube channels to Home Assistant.For every channel you add, it will create sensors for:</flag>
    <flag name="zabbix">The Zabbix integration to connect to a Zabbix monitoring instance via the Zabbix API.</flag>
    <flag name="zamg">The GeoSphere Austria platform uses meteorological details published by the Austrian weather service GeoSphere Austria.</flag>
    <flag name="zengge">The zengge integration allows you to integrate your Zengge Bluetooth bulbs into Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="zeroconf">The zeroconf integration will scan the network for supported devices and services. Discovered integrations will show up in the discovered section on the integrations page in the configuration panel. It will also make Home Assistant discoverable for other services in the network. Zeroconf is also sometimes known as Bonjour, Rendezvous, and Avahi.</flag>
    <flag name="zerproc">This integration discovers nearby Zerproc lights and adds them to Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="zestimate">The zestimate sensor allows one to track the Zestimate® value of properties using the Zillow API. According to Zillow’s website, a Zestimate® home valuation is Zillow’s estimated market value. It is not an appraisal. Use it as a starting point to determine a home’s value. The Zestimate® is provided by Zillow, a website primarily for listing homes to buy/sell/rent in the United States.</flag>
    <flag name="zeversolar">The Zeversolar integration allows you to collect and save data providing a historical overview of your Zeversolarproduction.</flag>
    <flag name="zha">The Zigbee Home Automation (ZHA) integration allows you to wirelessly connect many off-the-shelf Zigbee-based devices directly to Home Assistant, using one of many compatible hardware adapters called Zigbee coordinators.</flag>
    <flag name="zhong_hong">The zhong_hong climate platform lets you control Zhonghong HVAC Gateway Controller thermostats through Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="ziggo_mediabox_xl">The Ziggo Mediabox XL integration allows you to control a Ziggo Mediabox XL from Home Assistant.</flag>
    <flag name="zoneminder">The zoneminder integration sets up Home Assistant with your ZoneMinder instance.</flag>
    <flag name="zwave_js">The Z-Wave integration allows you to control a Z-Wave network from Home Assistant via the Z-Wave JS driver.</flag>
    <flag name="zwave_me">This integration allows you to control a Z-Wave network via the Z-Wave.Me Z-Way. It combines the performance and the power of the diagnostics tools built-in Z-Way with the flexibility of Home Assistant. The integration brings all Z-Way devices in Home Assistant (Z-Wave, Zigbee, EnOcean, HTTP based, and others).</flag>  </use>
</pkgmetadata>
